Acuerdo de Licencia para el Usuario Último ("EULA")
para PowerDVD

Fecha de última modificación: 9 de abril de 2015

No instale o utilice el software antes de leer y aceptar todas las condiciones de la licencia. La autorización para utilizar el software depende de su aceptación de las condiciones de la licencia. La instalación o utilización del software implica la aceptación por su parte de las condiciones de la licencia. La aceptación le obliga a cumplir las condiciones de la licencia en un contrato con CyberLink Corp. que puede llegar a legalizarse. 

*ACTIVACIÓN DEL CÓDEC
Cuando utilice por primera vez ciertas tecnologías esenciales para las funciones multimedia, la aplicación de software recopilará el número de serie de su sistema informático y la clave de producto (clave de CD) únicamente para fines de activación. 

*POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD
Algunos de nuestros productos pueden enviar un evento/señal anónimo al servidor de base de datos de CyberLink para recopilar información con el fin de mejorar la experiencia del usuario final, como, por ejemplo: 
-Cuando el usuario acepta o rechaza el CEIP (CyberLink Experience Improvement Program, Programa de mejora de la experiencia de CyberLink)/CPIP (CyberLink Product Improvement Program, Programa de mejora del producto de CyberLink); y
-Cuando nuestro producto se instala y/o se desinstala.

*SERVICIOS RELACIONADOS
Algunas de las funciones de nuestro producto pueden integrarse con servicios como MoovieLive y/o DirectorZone.  Si utiliza cualquier función de estos servicios, debe aceptar los términos de servicio y la política de privacidad correspondientes, que puede encontrar en: http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg ; http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg ; http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp y http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp  

* LICENCIA DEL SOFTWARE Y GARANTÍA LIMITADA
Esto es un acuerdo entre usted, el usuario último y CyberLink Corp. ("CyberLink"). Al utilizar este software, acepta estar obligado a cumplir las condiciones de este acuerdo.

Si acepta cumplir con estas condiciones, haga clic en "Sí". SI NO ACEPTA LAS CONDICIONES DE ESTE ACUERDO, NO UTILICE ESTE SOFTWARE Y ELIMÍNELO DE SU ORDENADOR INMEDIATAMENTE.

* * CONCESIÓN DE LICENCIA Y RESTRICCIONES DE USO
A continuación se incluyen las condiciones generales de licencia y las restricciones de uso seguidas de especificaciones concretas dependiendo del tipo de licencia que tenga.
CyberLink, como concedente, le concede, al titular de la licencia, un derecho no exclusivo de descargar y/o instalar el(los) programas de software de PowerDVD que acompaña(n) (de aquí en adelante el "SOFTWARE") en un determinado número de ordenadores/dispositivos de acuerdo con el número de licencias que haya adquirido y usar el SOFTWARE conforme a las condiciones de esta licencia. Usted acepta y confirma que puede recibir avisos de actualización y mejora del SOFTWARE o cualquier mensaje electrónico comercial durante el uso del SOFTWARE. Queda prohibido alquilar, transferir, licenciar, modificar, alterar, manipular, desmontar, descompilar o crear cualquier trabajo resultante del SOFTWARE, o eliminar nota alguna de los derechos de copia (copyright) o leyenda de patentes contenida en el SOFTWARE. También se prohíbe la reproducción del SOFTWARE a menos que sea por razones de copia de seguridad pudiendo haber una única copia. Usted acepta que la licencia de este SOFTWARE se confiere a su persona, sin que ello implique su venta. El SOFTWARE debe adquirirse de forma legal a través de CyberLink o de los proveedores autorizados por CyberLink, ya que en caso contrario no tendrá derecho a utilizar el SOFTWARE. Usted acepta que una vez que haga funcionar, utilice o instale el SOFTWARE, no podrá revenderlo ni distribuirlo a ninguna otra persona o entidad de acuerdo con la normativa correspondiente.  El hecho de que tenga permiso legal para revender el SOFTWARE dependerá de la ley de su lugar de residencia y de dónde se encuentre la persona a la que le vaya a transferir el software.  Normalmente, una reventa o distribución ocasionaría el cese automático de su licencia respecto al uso del SOFTWARE. Usted es el único responsable de los riesgos de no poder usar o instalar el SOFTWARE al NO comprar u obtener el SOFTWARE de CyberLink o de distribuidores o vendedores autorizados por CyberLink, o bien de utilizar SOFTWARE usado. Consulte el enlace [http://es.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/esp/index.jsp] para ver información sobre la compra de SOFTWARE en el sitio web oficial de CyberLink y la información de los distribuidores autorizados de CyberLink.
Tipos de licencia:
**USUARIO INDIVIDUAL
Si adquiere el SOFTWARE con una licencia individual, es para su propio uso según los términos generales descritos anteriormente.
**LICENCIA DE SITIO 
La licencia de sitio solo permite utilizar el SOFTWARE en una única ubicación.  El número máximo de usuarios está limitado por el acuerdo de la licencia de sitio.
	**LICENCIA DE VOLUMEN
Solo se puede instalar una copia por dispositivo.  Si usted es titular de una licencia de volumen, puede realizar varias copias de seguridad e instalar múltiples copias del SOFTWARE. El número total de copias permitidas se limitará a número máximo según la cantidad adquirida.
**LICENCIA DE EVALUACIÓN/PRUEBA
Solo se puede instalar una copia por dispositivo. El SOFTWARE se concede bajo licencia únicamente para fines de evaluación y/o prueba. Los derechos que se conceden en esta licencia cesarán tras un periodo de tiempo concreto y el SOFTWARE solo se podrá utilizar durante un tiempo limitado, después del cual puede quedar deshabilitado. Esta licencia es solo para uso no comercial.
**LICENCIA DE SUSCRIPCIÓN
El SOFTWARE se concede bajo licencia para fines de suscripción. Usted acepta que CyberLink pueda cambiar la versión del SOFTWARE proporcionado en cualquier momento sin que ello suponga ninguna responsabilidad ante usted. El acceso continuado al SOFTWARE de suscripción requiere disponer de una conexión a Internet activa, la recepción por parte de CyberLink de los pagos de suscripción recurrentes y la aceptación de las condiciones de uso y/o servicio del SOFTWARE de suscripción que se encuentra en el sitio de descarga. Los derechos que se conceden en esta licencia cesarán tras un periodo de tiempo concreto y el SOFTWARE solo se podrá utilizar durante un tiempo limitado, después del cual puede quedar deshabilitado.
**LICENCIA EDUCATIVA
El SOFTWARE se concede bajo licencia únicamente para fines educativos y no comerciales. Puede ser adquirida por colegios, universidades, alumnos y sus tutores legales, facultades, profesores, catedráticos, conferenciantes y cualquier otra institución, especialista o personal educativo.  
Si va a usar el SOFTWARE para fines comerciales, necesitará licencias adicionales para la siguiente lista no exhaustiva de tecnologías de terceros:
Tecnología 	Nombre de contrato 	Agente licenciatario / Concedente
       >BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA

CyberLink no concede bajo licencia los elementos anteriores para uso comercial y le aconsejamos que se ponga en contacto con los agentes licenciatarios correspondientes en las direcciones indicadas anteriormente para obtener más información.

*DISTRIBUCIÓN DE MPEG
QUEDA EXPRESAMENTE PROHIBIDO EL USO DE ESTE PRODUCTO DE CUALQUIER MODO DISTINTO DEL PERSONAL QUE CUMPLA CON EL ESTÁNDAR MPEG-2 PARA LA CODIFICACIÓN DE INFORMACIÓN DE VÍDEO PARA CONTENIDO MULTIMEDIA EMPAQUETADO SIN UNA LICENCIA CONFORME A LAS PATENTES APLICABLES EN LA CARTERA DE PATENTES DE MPEG-2. DICHA LICENCIA ESTÁ DISPONIBLE POR PARTE DE MPEG-LA, LLC EN LA DIRECCIÓN INDICADA ANTERIORMENTE.
ESTE PRODUCTO SE CONCEDE BAJO LICENCIA DE LA CARTERA DE PATENTES DE AVC PARA EL USO PERSONAL Y NO COMERCIAL DE UN USUARIO PARA (i) CODIFICAR VÍDEO CONFORME AL ESTÁNDAR AVC (“VÍDEO AVC”) Y/O (ii) DECODIFICAR VÍDEO AVC CODIFICADO POR UN USUARIO QUE REALICE UNA ACTIVIDAD PERSONAL Y NO COMERCIAL Y/O OBTENIDO DE UN PROVEEDOR DE VÍDEO CON LICENCIA PARA PROPORCIONAR VÍDEO AVC. LAS LICENCIAS NO SE CONCEDEN PARA NINGÚN OTRO USO, NI ESTÁN DIRIGIDAS DE FORMA IMPLÍCITA A NINGÚN OTRO USO. SE PUEDE SOLICITAR MÁS INFORMACIÓN A MPEG-LA.
Usted también reconoce que no se otorgan derechos ni se ampliarán para el uso del SOFTWARE con contenido de vídeo MPEG-4 a menos que dicho contenido MPEG-4 le sea vendido o proporcionado por un tenedor de la licencia del distribuidor de contenidos bajo las reclamaciones esenciales de MPEG-4 para realizar tal venta o entrega.

* PROPIEDAD DEL SOFTWARE. 
CyberLink mantiene el copyright, título y propiedad del SOFTWARE y el material escrito ("Documentación") sin tener en cuenta la forma o medios en los que puedan existir el original y otras copias.

* ACTUALIZACIONES. 
Si esta copia del SOFTWARE es una actualización de una versión anterior del mismo, se considerará como un intercambio de licencia. Usted acepta con la instalación y uso de esta copia del SOFTWARE que se anula voluntariamente su anterior EULA y que no continuará utilizando la versión anterior del SOFTWARE ni la traspasará ni distribuirá a otra persona o entidad.

* UTILIZACIÓN DE CONTENIDO MULTIMEDIA LICENCIADO POR TERCEROS
Puede utilizar imágenes, audio, vídeo, miniaturas u otro contenido multimedia (contenido multimedia), si lo hay, incluido en el SOFTWARE, que puede estar licenciado por terceros, para demostrar o completar su trabajo creado a través del SOFTWARE; siempre que no utilice el contenido multimedia  de manera ilegal, comercial o inmoral, ni conceda su derecho de uso a terceros. CyberLink no ofrece garantía alguna para estos elementos de contenido multimedia de terceros y rechaza cualquier responsabilidad en la máxima medida que permita la ley.  

* GARANTÍA LIMITADA. 
CyberLink garantiza que el medio por el que el SOFTWARE se vende está libre de defectos materiales y de mano de obra bajo un uso normal y durante noventa (90) días a partir de la fecha de entrega. Si hubiese algún defecto en el medio (CD/DVD-ROM), la única responsabilidad de CyberLink sería reemplazar el medio defectuoso siempre que se devolviese a CyberLink o al proveedor con su factura con fecha y se comprobase su defecto. En caso de que CyberLink no pueda reemplazar el medio defectuoso, CyberLink, a su propio criterio, le devolverá el dinero al finalizar esta licencia o reemplazará su software con una versión nueva.

ESTE SOFTWARE Y LA DOCUMENTACIÓN QUE LE ACOMPAÑA (INCLUYENDO LAS INSTRUCCIONES DE USO) SE FACILITAN "TAL CUAL" SIN GARANTÍA DE NINGÚN TIPO Y SIN PROTECCIÓN. ADEMÁS, CYBERLINK NO JUSTIFICA, GARANTIZA O REPRESENTA EN MODO ALGUNO EL USO, O LOS RESULTADOS DEL USO, DEL SOFTWARE O DOCUMENTACIÓN EN LO REFERENTE A LA EXACTITUD, PRECISIÓN, FIABILIDAD, VIGENCIA, U OTROS ASPECTOS. USTED ASUME LA TOTALIDAD DEL RIESGO POR LOS RESULTADOS Y RENDIMIENTO DE ESTE SOFTWARE. SI EL SOFTWARE O LA DOCUMENTACIÓN SON DEFECTUOSOS, USTED, Y NO CYBERLINK NI SUS VENDEDORES, DISTRIBUIDORES, AGENTES O EMPLEADOS, ASUME EL COSTE TOTAL DEL SERVICIO, REPARACIÓN O CORRECCIÓN NECESARIOS. 

CYBERLINK RECHAZA TODAS LAS DEMÁS GARANTÍAS SOBRE ESTE PRODUCTO DE CYBERLINK, EXPRESAS O IMPLÍCITAS, INCLUIDAS PERO NO LIMITADAS A LAS GARANTÍAS IMPLÍCITAS DE MERCANTIBILIDAD, ADAPTACIÓN PARA PROPÓSITOS PARTICULARES Y DE NO INFRACCIÓN, SIN INFLUIR SI HAN SIDO REALIZADAS O NO POR CYBERLINK. CYBERLINK NO GARANTIZA QUE EL SOFTWARE NO FALLE O TENGA ERRORES. NINGUNA INFORMACIÓN POR ESCRITO O AVISO OFRECIDO POR CYBERLINK, SUS VENDEDORES, DISTRIBUIDORES, AGENTES O EMPLEADOS CREARÁ UNA GARANTÍA O DE ALGÚN MODO AUMENTARÁ LOS LÍMITES DE ESTA GARANTÍA Y POR TANTO NO DEBE CONTAR CON TAL INFORMACIÓN O AVISO. 

NI CYBERLINK NI NADIE MÁS QUE HAYA TOMADO PARTE EN LA CREACIÓN, PRODUCCIÓN O DISTRIBUCIÓN DE ESTE PRODUCTO SE HARÁ RESPONSABLE POR LOS DAÑOS DIRECTOS, INDIRECTOS, CONSECUENTES O INCIDENTALES (INCLUYENDO DAÑOS POR PÉRDIDA DE BENEFICIOS, INTERRUPCIÓN DEL NEGOCIO, PÉRDIDA DE DATOS U OTRA PÉRDIDA ECONÓMICA) QUE PROVENGAN DEL USO O LA INCAPACIDAD DE USO DE DICHO PRODUCTO AUN CUANDO CYBERLINK HAYA AVISADO DE LA POSIBILIDAD DE TALES DAÑOS.

Si llegase a existir cualquier otra garantía, ésta deberá estar limitada en duración a noventa (90) días a partir de la fecha de entrega. La responsabilidad de CyberLink por los posibles daños hacia usted o cualquier otra persona no excederá bajo ningún concepto la cantidad pagada por la licencia para el uso del SOFTWARE.

Usted acepta indemnizar y mantener a CyberLink exento de cualquier reclamación, procedimiento, daño, coste o gasto resultante del uso del SOFTWARE con cualquier fin ilegal así como del incumplimiento del presente Acuerdo de licencia para usuario final.

Si este acuerdo queda anulado, debe destruir el software, la documentación y todas las copias enseguida y eliminar el software de su disco duro u otro sistema de almacenamiento.

Este acuerdo constituye un acuerdo íntegro entre usted y CyberLink Corp. Este acuerdo será dirigido e interpretado según las leyes de Taiwán en beneficio de CyberLink, sus sucesores y asignados. 

Cualquier reclamación o disputa entre usted y CyberLink o un agente, empleado, sucesor o asignado de CyberLink, relacionada con este acuerdo o no, y cualquier reclamación o disputa relacionada con este acuerdo o la relación u obligaciones contempladas bajo este acuerdo, incluyendo la validez de esta cláusula de arbitraje, será resuelta en Taipei, Taiwán, según el Acto de Arbitraje de Taiwán. 

Esta versión localizada del EULA sirve sólo como referencia. En caso de discrepancias entre la versión localizada y la versión inglesa, prevalecerá la versión inglesa.

End User License Agreement ("EULA")
For PowerDVD

Date last modified: April 9, 2015.

Do not install or use the software until you have read and accepted all of the license terms. Permission to use the software is conditional upon your agreeing to the license terms. Installation or use of the software by you will be deemed to be acceptance of the license terms. Acceptance will bind you to the license terms in a legally enforceable contract with CyberLink Corp.

*CODEC ACTIVATION
When you use certain technologies essential to multi-media functions for the first time, the software application will collect the serial number of your computer system and the product key (CD key) for activation purposes only. 

*PRIVACY POLICY
Some of our products may send an anonymous event/signal to CyberLink’s backend server to collect information for the purpose of improving the end user experience, such as for example: 
-When user opts in or out of the CEIP (CyberLink Experience Improvement Program)/CPIP (CyberLink Product Improvement Program); and
-When our product is installed and/or uninstalled.

*RELATED SERVICES
Some of our product features may integrate with services such as MoovieLive and/or DirectorZone.  If you use any features from these services then you must agree to the terms of service and privacy policy thereof; which can be found at: http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg ; http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg ; http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp and http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp 

* SOFTWARE LICENSE AND LIMITED WARRANTY
This EULA is an agreement between you, the end user, and CyberLink Corp. ("CyberLink"). By using this software, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA.

If you agree to abide by these conditions, please click "Yes". IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS EULA, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SOFTWARE AND PROMPTLY REMOVE IT FROM YOUR COMPUTER.

* GRANT OF LICENSE & USAGE RESTRICTIONS
Below are the general license terms and usage restrictions followed by specific provisions depending on the type of license you have.
CyberLink, as licensor, grants to you, the licensee, a non-exclusive right to download and/or install the accompanying PowerDVD software program(s) (hereinafter the "SOFTWARE") on a certain number of computer(s)/ device(s) in accordance with the number of the license(s) you purchased and use the SOFTWARE in accordance with the terms contained in this license. You agree and acknowledge that you may receive SOFTWARE update, upgrade notices or any commercial electronic messages during the use of SOFTWARE. You shall not rent, lease, sublicense, modify, alter, reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile, or create any derivative work of the SOFTWARE, or remove any copyright notice or proprietary legend contained in the SOFTWARE. You shall not reproduce the SOFTWARE unless for backup purposes and limited to one copy only. You acknowledge this SOFTWARE is licensed to you, not sold to you. The SOFTWARE must be lawfully acquired from CyberLink or through CyberLink’s authorized resellers otherwise you do not have a right to use the SOFTWARE. You agree that once SOFTWARE is operated, used or installed; you may not resell or distribute it to another person or entity subject to the relevant statutes.  Whether you are legally allowed to resell the SOFTWARE will depend on the law of your place of residence or where the transferee is located.  Generally a resale or distribution will cause an automatic termination of your license to use the SOFTWARE. You own and are responsible for the risks of inability to use or install the SOFTWARE in purchasing or obtaining the SOFTWARE NOT from CyberLink, CyberLink’s authorized distributors or resellers or for used SOFTWARE.  Please refer to the link [http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp] for the SOFTWARE purchase information in CyberLink’s official website and for the information of CyberLink’s authorized distributors.
       **INDIVIDUAL CONSUMER
If you acquire the SOFTWARE under an individual license it is for your own use under the general terms above.
       **SITE LICENSE 
Site licensed SOFTWARE is licensed to be used in a single location.  The maximum number of users is limited by the site license agreement.
	**VOLUME LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed.  If you are the volume license holder then you may make multiple back-up copies and install multiple seats of the SOFTWARE. The total number of licensed copies will be limited to a capped number according to the purchased quantity in bulk.
       **EVALUATION/TRIAL LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed. The SOFTWARE is licensed for evaluation and/or trial purposes only. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled. This license is for non-commercial use.
       **SUBSCRIPTION LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for subscription purposes. You agree that CyberLink may change the version of the SOFTWARE provided to you at any time without liability to you. Ongoing access to Subscription SOFTWARE requires a working internet connection, CyberLink’s receipt of recurring subscription payments and agreement to the terms of use and/or service for Subscription SOFTWARE to be found on the downloading site. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled.
	**EDUCATIONAL LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for educational purposes and non-commercial use only. It may be purchased by schools, universities, students and their legal guardians, faculty, teachers, professors, lecturers and any other educational institutions, scholars or staff.  

If you are going to use the SOFTWARE for commercial purposes then additional licenses will be needed for the following non-exhaustive list of third party technologies:
>BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA


CyberLink does not license the above items for commercial use and you are advised to approach the relevant licensing agents at the above addresses for more information.

*MPEG DISTRIBUTION
ANY USE OF THIS PRODUCT IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN PERSONAL USE THAT COMPLIES WITH THE MPEG-2 STANDARD FOR ENCODING VIDEO INFORMATION FOR PACKAGED MEDIA IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED WITHOUT A LICENSE UNDER APPLICABLE PATENTS IN THE MPEG-2 PATENT PORTFOLIO, WHICH LICENSE IS AVAILABLE FROM MPEG-LA,LLC AT THE ADDRESS ABOVE.
THIS PRODUCT IS LICENSED UNDER THE AVC PATENT PORTFOLIO LICENSE FOR THE PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL USE OF A CONSUMER TO (i) ENCODE VIDEO IN COMLIANCE WITH THE AVC STANDARD (“AVC VIDEO”) AND/OR (ii) DECODE AVC VIDEO THAT WAS ENCODED BY A CONSUMER ENGAGED IN A PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY AND/OR WAS OBTAINED FROM A VIDEO PROVIDER LICENSED TO PROVIDE AVC VIDEO. NO LICENSE IS GRANTED OR SHALL BE IMPLIED FOR ANY OTHER USE. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM MPEG-LA.
You also acknowledge that no rights are granted or may be extended to you to use the SOFTWARE with MPEG-4 Video Content unless such MPEG-4 Content is sold or delivered to you by a content outlet licensed under the MPEG-4 Essential Claims to make such sale or delivery. 

* OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE
CyberLink retains the copyright, title and ownership of the SOFTWARE and the written materials ("Documentation") regardless of the form or media in or on which the original and other copies may exist.

* UPGRADES
If this copy of the SOFTWARE is an upgrade from an earlier version of the SOFTWARE, it is provided to you on a license exchange basis. Upon your installation and use of this copy of the SOFTWARE, you agree to voluntarily terminate your earlier EULA and you will not continue to use the earlier version of the SOFTWARE or resell or distribute it to another person or entity.

* USE OF MEDIA CONTENT LICENSED BY THIRD PARTIES
You may use pictures, audio, video, thumbnails or other media content (media content), if any, provided in the SOFTWARE, which may be licensed from third parties, to demonstrate or complete your work created by the use of the SOFTWARE; provided that you should not use the media content in any illegal, commercial or immoral manner, nor shall you grant your right to use to any third party. CyberLink does not provide any warranty or representation to these media content items from third parties and disclaims all liabilities to the maximum extent allowed by law.  

* LIMITED WARRANTY
CyberLink warrants the media on which the SOFTWARE is furnished to be free of defects in material and workmanship, under normal use, for a period of ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. If there is a defect in the media (CD/DVD-ROM), CyberLink's sole liability shall be to replace the defective media, which has been returned to CyberLink or the supplier with your dated invoice and is shown to be defective. In the event that CyberLink is unable to replace defective media, CyberLink shall at its sole discretion either refund your money upon your termination of this license or replace it with the newer version of the same software.

THIS SOFTWARE AND ACCOMPANYING DOCUMENTATION (INCLUDING INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE) ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND ARE NOT FAIL-SAFE. FURTHER, CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE, OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE, OF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IN TERMS OF CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CURRENTNESS, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE SOFTWARE IS ASSUMED BY YOU. IF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IS DEFECTIVE, YOU, AND NOT CYBERLINK OR ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS, OR EMPLOYEES, ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICE, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

CYBERLINK DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER IT IS MADE BY CYBERLINK, ON THIS CYBERLINK PRODUCT. CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY CYBERLINK, ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY OR IN ANY WAY INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THIS WARRANTY AND YOU MAY NOT RELY ON ANY SUCH INFORMATION OR ADVICE. 

NEITHER CYBERLINK NOR ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THIS PRODUCT SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE SUCH PRODUCT EVEN IF CYBERLINK HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Should any other warranties be found to exist, such warranties shall be limited in duration to ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. In no event will CyberLink's liability for any damages to you or any other person exceed the amount paid for the license to use the SOFTWARE.

You agree to bear the full, complete, and sole responsibility for using the SOFTWARE for any purpose. You also agree to indemnify and hold CyberLink harmless from any claims, proceedings, damages, costs, and expenses resulting from your use of the SOFTWARE for any illegal purpose or violation of this EULA.

Upon termination of this EULA, you should destroy the SOFTWARE and the Documentation and all the copies thereof and remove and delete the SOFTWARE from your hard disk or other storage device.

This EULA constitutes the entire agreement between you and CyberLink Corp. This EULA shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Taiwan and shall benefit CyberLink, its successors and assigns. 

Any claim or dispute between you and CyberLink or against any agent, employee, successor or assign of CyberLink, whether related to this EUL A or otherwise, and any claim or dispute related to this EULA or the relationship or duties contemplated under this EULA, including the validity of this arbitration clause, shall be resolved in Taipei, Taiwan, pursuant to the Taiwan Arbitration Act. 

This localized version of the EULA is for reference only. In case of inconsistencies between the localized version and the English version, the English version will prevail.