使用者授權合約 (EULA)
適用於 PowerDVD

最近修改日期: 2015 年 4 月 9 日

在閱讀並接受本授權合約所有條款之前，請勿安裝或使用本軟體。在 貴用戶同意此授權合約條款後，才具有使用本軟體之許可權。若 貴用戶逕行安裝或使用本軟體者，視為 貴用戶接受本授權合約條款。

*轉碼器啟用
您第一次使用多媒體功能某些重要的技術時，本軟體應用程式將收集電腦系統序號及產品金鑰 (CD 金鑰)，僅用於啟動用途。 

*隱私權原則
我們的部份產品會傳送匿名事件/訊號到訊連科技的後端伺服器，收集改善使用者體驗的資訊，例如： 
- 使用者選擇參加或退出 CEIP (訊連科技體驗改善計劃)/CPIP (訊連科技產品改善計劃)；以及
- 安裝和/或解除安裝我們的產品時。

*相關服務
我們部份的產品功能可整合 MoovieLive 及/或 DirectorZone 等服務。  如果您使用這些服務的功能，您必須同意服務條款和隱私權原則，這些可在下列位置找到： http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg、http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg、http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp 及 http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp  

* 軟體授權合約
本 EULA 係 貴用戶 (使用者) 與訊連科技股份有限公司 (以下簡稱「訊連科技」) 之間的協議。當 貴用戶安裝或使用本訊連科技所有之軟體(以下簡稱「本軟體」)，即視為 貴用戶接受本 EULA 之規範。

若 貴用戶同意接受本授權合約條款，請按一下「是」。如果 貴用戶不同意本 EULA，則請勿安裝本軟體，並請將它從電腦中移除。

* 授權範圍及使用限制
以下為依據您授權類型制定之特定條款的一般授權條款及使用限制。
訊連科技茲非專屬授權 貴用戶得在單一或特定數量 (視 貴用戶購買之授權數目而定) 之電腦/裝置下載及/或安裝 PowerDVD 軟體，並按照本授權合約之規定與限制使用「本軟體」。您同意且知悉使用「軟體」的過程中，可能會收到「軟體」更新、升級通知，或任何廣告電子訊息。貴用戶不得出租、轉授權、修改、變更、逆向工程、解譯或反組譯「本軟體」，或是創作「本軟體」之衍生著作，亦不可移除「本軟體」中所包含之任何著作權聲明或資訊。貴用戶亦不得對「本軟體」進行重製，但得為備份之單一用途下製作一份拷貝。貴用戶承認只取得「本軟體」之授權，而非賣斷。必須經由訊連科技或授權經銷商合法取得「本軟體」，否則您無權使用「本軟體」。貴用戶同意，按照相關法規，在操作、使用或安裝「本軟體」後，不得再將之轉售予他人或其他實體。您是否依法得以轉售「本軟體」取決於您居住地或承買人所在地的法律。一般而言，轉售或散佈行為將自動終止 貴用戶使用「本軟體」之授權。若您並非從訊連或訊連授權代理商或經銷商購買「軟體」或二手「軟體」，您瞭解且對無法使用或安裝「軟體」的風險負責。請參閱連結 [http://tw.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/cht/index.jsp]，以瞭解訊連官方網站上的「軟體」購買資訊，以及訊連授權經銷商的資訊。  
授權類型：
**個人消費者
如果您透過個人授權取得「本軟體」，將按照以上的一般條款專供您個人使用。
**地點授權
獲得地點授權的「本軟體」經授權在單一地點使用。使用者人數上限以地點授權合約為限。
**大量授權
各個裝置只能安裝一份。如果您是大量授權擁有人，則您可進行多次備份拷貝，並安裝「本軟體」多個基座。授權拷貝總數僅限於以大量購買數量為準之數量上限。
**評估/試用授權
各個裝置只能安裝一份。僅授權「本軟體」用於評估及/或試用用途。在指定的時間週期及「本軟體」使用時限過後，此處授予您之權利將終止，且「本軟體」將在到期後停用。此授權僅供非商業用途使用。
**訂閱授權
可授權「本軟體」用於訂閱用途。您同意訊連科技得隨時變更提供予您的「本軟體」版本，而不須為您負責。接下來進行的「軟體」訂閱需要有運作正常的網際網路連線，訊連科技的週期性訂閱付款收據，以及「軟體」訂閱之使用和/或服務條款的合約可在下載網站上找到。在指定的時間週期及「本軟體」使用時限過後，此處授予您之權利將終止，且「本軟體」將在到期後停用。
**教育授權
僅授權「本軟體」用於教育用途及非商業用途。學校、大學、學生及其法定監護人、系所、教師、教授、講師及其他任何教育機構、學者或職員均可購買。  
若您將使用「軟體」進行商業用途，則下列舉例說明的協力廠商技術需要另行授權：
技術
合約名稱
授權代理商 / 授權人
       >BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA

訊連科技並未授權上述條款用於商業用途，建議您洽詢上述地址的相關授權代理商，瞭解詳細資訊。

*MPEG 散佈
若未獲得 MPEG-2 專利組合相關專利的授權，嚴禁將本產品用於將 MPEG-2 標準用於套裝媒體視訊資訊編碼的個人用途以外的任何用途，如需取得 MPEG-LA, LLC 的授權，請洽詢上列地址。
本產品係依據 AVC 專利組合授權用於消費者的個人非商業用途，包括：(i) 使用 AVC 標準 (「AVC 視訊」) 進行視訊編碼，以及/或者 (ii) 將消費者編碼的個人非商業活動 AVC 視訊以及/或者向授權提供 AVC 視訊的視訊提供者取得的 AVC 視訊解碼。 並未針對其他任何用途授予授權，亦不得暗示可針對其他任何用途獲得授權。 如需詳細資訊，請洽詢 MPEG-LA。
此外，除非 MPEG-4 內容係購自或取自獲得 MPEG-4 Essential Claims 授權可販售或交付此等內容之商店，否則您承認不具使用本「軟體」播放 MPEG-4 視訊內容之其他權利或延伸權利。

* 權利歸屬
「本軟體」之著作權及其他智慧財產權等相關權利或利益(包括但不限於現已取得或未來可取得之著作權、專利權、商標權、營業秘密等)皆為甲方所有。

* 升級
若「本軟體」是從舊版「軟體」升級而來，則是以授權交換方式提供予您。一旦安裝使用「本軟體」，即同意自願終止舊版使用者授權合約，並且將不再使用舊版「軟體」，亦不轉售或散佈予他人或其他實體。

* 使用第三人授權之媒體內容
如 貴用戶欲使用「本軟體」創作作品，貴用戶得使用「本軟體」內第三人授權之任何圖庫、視訊、音訊、縮圖或其他媒體內容 (媒體內容)，但 貴用戶不得非法、商業或違反公序良俗之使用該等媒體內容，亦不可將該等圖庫轉授權予任何第三人。 訊連科技對該等媒體內容項目不提供任何保證，且不擔負法定程度以外之任何責任。  

* 保證
訊連科技保證自 貴用戶購得「本軟體」後九十 (90) 日內（下稱「保證期間」），於一般正常使用下，儲存「本軟體」之媒體無重大瑕疵。若該媒體 (CD/DVD-ROM) 有任何瑕疵，訊連科技同意於保證期間內提供更換服務，但 貴用戶須將損壞之媒體連同發票退回訊連科技或供應商。如訊連科技無法更換損壞之媒體，則將退還購買費用或更換「本軟體」之更新版軟體，並同時終止本授權合約。前述之更換服務乃訊連科技所負擔之唯一瑕疵擔保責任。

「本軟體」及其隨附之文件（包含使用說明）僅以「原狀」提供，不具任何形式之擔保非故障無礙。此外，訊連科技亦不對「本軟體」或其文件之使用或使用結果之正確性及可靠性提供任何保證。「本軟體」及其效能表現所產生之所有風險皆由 貴用戶承擔。如因「本軟體」或其文件之瑕疵而致 貴用戶受有損害， 貴客戶應自行負擔所有修復或其他服務費用，訊連科技或其經銷商、配銷商、代理商或員工不負擔此責任或義務。 

訊連科技亦不為其他明示或默示擔保，其包含，但不限於，有關「本軟體」之適售性、符合特定目的之使用、以及無侵害他人權利情事者。訊連科技且不保證「本軟體」之執行不會中斷或全無錯誤。縱訊連科技及其經銷商、配銷商、代理商或員工提出任何口頭或書面之保證，亦不構成任何保證責任。

訊連科技或其供應商對於 貴用戶因使用或無法使用「本軟體」，或所提供或無法提供支援服務所發生之任何直接、間接、附隨或衍生性損害 (包括營業利益損失、營業中斷、營業資料損失或其他金錢損失) 不負任何損害賠償責任。

訊連科技對 貴用戶如有任何損害賠償責任，則以 貴用戶取得「本軟體」之代價為其責任上限。

無論 貴用戶為任何目的使用「本軟體」， 貴用戶同意獨自承擔完全之責任。 貴用戶亦同意保護訊連科技，並使訊連科技免受任何肇因於 貴用戶任何非法使用本軟體或違反本 EULA 所生之權利主張、程序、損害、成本和支出。

其他條款。於本 EULA 終止時， 貴用戶應銷毀「本軟體」及其文件，以及所有現存之副本拷貝，並從硬碟或其他儲存媒體中將「本軟體」移除或刪除。

本 EULA 為 貴用戶與訊連科技之間對「本軟體」之完整合意，並以台灣法為準據法，且對於訊連科技及 貴用戶之繼受人均有適用。

貴用戶與訊連科技或其代理商、員工、繼受人或受讓人之間如有任何爭議，無論是否因本 EULA 而起，包括仲裁條款之合法性爭議等，皆應以台灣台北為仲裁地，且受台灣仲裁法之規範。

本授權合約翻譯版本僅供參考。若翻譯之版本與英文版本不一致，則以英文版本為準。

End User License Agreement ("EULA")
For PowerDVD

Date last modified: April 9, 2015.

Do not install or use the software until you have read and accepted all of the license terms. Permission to use the software is conditional upon your agreeing to the license terms. Installation or use of the software by you will be deemed to be acceptance of the license terms. Acceptance will bind you to the license terms in a legally enforceable contract with CyberLink Corp.

*CODEC ACTIVATION
When you use certain technologies essential to multi-media functions for the first time, the software application will collect the serial number of your computer system and the product key (CD key) for activation purposes only. 

*PRIVACY POLICY
Some of our products may send an anonymous event/signal to CyberLink’s backend server to collect information for the purpose of improving the end user experience, such as for example: 
-When user opts in or out of the CEIP (CyberLink Experience Improvement Program)/CPIP (CyberLink Product Improvement Program); and
-When our product is installed and/or uninstalled.

*RELATED SERVICES
Some of our product features may integrate with services such as MoovieLive and/or DirectorZone.  If you use any features from these services then you must agree to the terms of service and privacy policy thereof; which can be found at: http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg ; http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg ; http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp and http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp 

* SOFTWARE LICENSE AND LIMITED WARRANTY
This EULA is an agreement between you, the end user, and CyberLink Corp. ("CyberLink"). By using this software, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA.

If you agree to abide by these conditions, please click "Yes". IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS EULA, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SOFTWARE AND PROMPTLY REMOVE IT FROM YOUR COMPUTER.

* GRANT OF LICENSE & USAGE RESTRICTIONS
Below are the general license terms and usage restrictions followed by specific provisions depending on the type of license you have.
CyberLink, as licensor, grants to you, the licensee, a non-exclusive right to download and/or install the accompanying PowerDVD software program(s) (hereinafter the "SOFTWARE") on a certain number of computer(s)/ device(s) in accordance with the number of the license(s) you purchased and use the SOFTWARE in accordance with the terms contained in this license. You agree and acknowledge that you may receive SOFTWARE update, upgrade notices or any commercial electronic messages during the use of SOFTWARE. You shall not rent, lease, sublicense, modify, alter, reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile, or create any derivative work of the SOFTWARE, or remove any copyright notice or proprietary legend contained in the SOFTWARE. You shall not reproduce the SOFTWARE unless for backup purposes and limited to one copy only. You acknowledge this SOFTWARE is licensed to you, not sold to you. The SOFTWARE must be lawfully acquired from CyberLink or through CyberLink’s authorized resellers otherwise you do not have a right to use the SOFTWARE. You agree that once SOFTWARE is operated, used or installed; you may not resell or distribute it to another person or entity subject to the relevant statutes.  Whether you are legally allowed to resell the SOFTWARE will depend on the law of your place of residence or where the transferee is located.  Generally a resale or distribution will cause an automatic termination of your license to use the SOFTWARE. You own and are responsible for the risks of inability to use or install the SOFTWARE in purchasing or obtaining the SOFTWARE NOT from CyberLink, CyberLink’s authorized distributors or resellers or for used SOFTWARE.  Please refer to the link [http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp] for the SOFTWARE purchase information in CyberLink’s official website and for the information of CyberLink’s authorized distributors.  
License Types:
       **INDIVIDUAL CONSUMER
If you acquire the SOFTWARE under an individual license it is for your own use under the general terms above.
       **SITE LICENSE 
Site licensed SOFTWARE is licensed to be used in a single location.  The maximum number of users is limited by the site license agreement.
	**VOLUME LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed.  If you are the volume license holder then you may make multiple back-up copies and install multiple seats of the SOFTWARE. The total number of licensed copies will be limited to a capped number according to the purchased quantity in bulk.
       **EVALUATION/TRIAL LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed. The SOFTWARE is licensed for evaluation and/or trial purposes only. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled. This license is for non-commercial use.
       **SUBSCRIPTION LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for subscription purposes. You agree that CyberLink may change the version of the SOFTWARE provided to you at any time without liability to you. Ongoing access to Subscription SOFTWARE requires a working internet connection, CyberLink’s receipt of recurring subscription payments and agreement to the terms of use and/or service for Subscription SOFTWARE to be found on the downloading site. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled.
	**EDUCATIONAL LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for educational purposes and non-commercial use only. It may be purchased by schools, universities, students and their legal guardians, faculty, teachers, professors, lecturers and any other educational institutions, scholars or staff.  

If you are going to use the SOFTWARE for commercial purposes then additional licenses will be needed for the following non-exhaustive list of third party technologies:
>BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA


CyberLink does not license the above items for commercial use and you are advised to approach the relevant licensing agents at the above addresses for more information.

*MPEG DISTRIBUTION
ANY USE OF THIS PRODUCT IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN PERSONAL USE THAT COMPLIES WITH THE MPEG-2 STANDARD FOR ENCODING VIDEO INFORMATION FOR PACKAGED MEDIA IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED WITHOUT A LICENSE UNDER APPLICABLE PATENTS IN THE MPEG-2 PATENT PORTFOLIO, WHICH LICENSE IS AVAILABLE FROM MPEG-LA,LLC AT THE ADDRESS ABOVE.
THIS PRODUCT IS LICENSED UNDER THE AVC PATENT PORTFOLIO LICENSE FOR THE PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL USE OF A CONSUMER TO (i) ENCODE VIDEO IN COMLIANCE WITH THE AVC STANDARD (“AVC VIDEO”) AND/OR (ii) DECODE AVC VIDEO THAT WAS ENCODED BY A CONSUMER ENGAGED IN A PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY AND/OR WAS OBTAINED FROM A VIDEO PROVIDER LICENSED TO PROVIDE AVC VIDEO. NO LICENSE IS GRANTED OR SHALL BE IMPLIED FOR ANY OTHER USE. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM MPEG-LA.
You also acknowledge that no rights are granted or may be extended to you to use the SOFTWARE with MPEG-4 Video Content unless such MPEG-4 Content is sold or delivered to you by a content outlet licensed under the MPEG-4 Essential Claims to make such sale or delivery. 

* OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE
CyberLink retains the copyright, title and ownership of the SOFTWARE and the written materials ("Documentation") regardless of the form or media in or on which the original and other copies may exist.

* UPGRADES
If this copy of the SOFTWARE is an upgrade from an earlier version of the SOFTWARE, it is provided to you on a license exchange basis. Upon your installation and use of this copy of the SOFTWARE, you agree to voluntarily terminate your earlier EULA and you will not continue to use the earlier version of the SOFTWARE or resell or distribute it to another person or entity.

* USE OF MEDIA CONTENT LICENSED BY THIRD PARTIES
You may use pictures, audio, video, thumbnails or other media content (media content), if any, provided in the SOFTWARE, which may be licensed from third parties, to demonstrate or complete your work created by the use of the SOFTWARE; provided that you should not use the media content in any illegal, commercial or immoral manner, nor shall you grant your right to use to any third party. CyberLink does not provide any warranty or representation to these media content items from third parties and disclaims all liabilities to the maximum extent allowed by law.  

* LIMITED WARRANTY
CyberLink warrants the media on which the SOFTWARE is furnished to be free of defects in material and workmanship, under normal use, for a period of ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. If there is a defect in the media (CD/DVD-ROM), CyberLink's sole liability shall be to replace the defective media, which has been returned to CyberLink or the supplier with your dated invoice and is shown to be defective. In the event that CyberLink is unable to replace defective media, CyberLink shall at its sole discretion either refund your money upon your termination of this license or replace it with the newer version of the same software.

THIS SOFTWARE AND ACCOMPANYING DOCUMENTATION (INCLUDING INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE) ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND ARE NOT FAIL-SAFE. FURTHER, CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE, OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE, OF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IN TERMS OF CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CURRENTNESS, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE SOFTWARE IS ASSUMED BY YOU. IF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IS DEFECTIVE, YOU, AND NOT CYBERLINK OR ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS, OR EMPLOYEES, ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICE, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

CYBERLINK DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER IT IS MADE BY CYBERLINK, ON THIS CYBERLINK PRODUCT. CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY CYBERLINK, ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY OR IN ANY WAY INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THIS WARRANTY AND YOU MAY NOT RELY ON ANY SUCH INFORMATION OR ADVICE. 

NEITHER CYBERLINK NOR ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THIS PRODUCT SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE SUCH PRODUCT EVEN IF CYBERLINK HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Should any other warranties be found to exist, such warranties shall be limited in duration to ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. In no event will CyberLink's liability for any damages to you or any other person exceed the amount paid for the license to use the SOFTWARE.

You agree to bear the full, complete, and sole responsibility for using the SOFTWARE for any purpose. You also agree to indemnify and hold CyberLink harmless from any claims, proceedings, damages, costs, and expenses resulting from your use of the SOFTWARE for any illegal purpose or violation of this EULA.

Upon termination of this EULA, you should destroy the SOFTWARE and the Documentation and all the copies thereof and remove and delete the SOFTWARE from your hard disk or other storage device.

This EULA constitutes the entire agreement between you and CyberLink Corp. This EULA shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Taiwan and shall benefit CyberLink, its successors and assigns. 

Any claim or dispute between you and CyberLink or against any agent, employee, successor or assign of CyberLink, whether related to this EUL A or otherwise, and any claim or dispute related to this EULA or the relationship or duties contemplated under this EULA, including the validity of this arbitration clause, shall be resolved in Taipei, Taiwan, pursuant to the Taiwan Arbitration Act. 

This localized version of the EULA is for reference only. In case of inconsistencies between the localized version and the English version, the English version will prevail.