用户授权合约 (EULA)

最后修改日期: 2015年4月9日
用于 PowerDVD

在阅读并接受本授权合约所有的条款之前，请勿安装或使用此软件。在用户同意此授权条款时，才具有使用此软件的权限。安装或使用此软件即表示用户接受此授权条款。 

*编解码器激活
当您首次使用某些非常重要的多媒体功能技术时，本软件应用程序将仅出于激活目的而收集您计算机系统的序列号和产品密钥 (CD 密钥)。 

* 隐私政策
我们部分产品可能会出于改善最终用户体验的目的向讯连科技的后端服务器发送匿名事件 / 信号以收集信息，例如： 
- 用户选择参加或退出 CEIP (讯连科技体验改善计划) / CPIP (讯连科技产品改善计划) 时；
- 当我们的产品安装和 / 或卸载时。

*相关服务
我们部分产品功能可能整合了诸如 MoovieLive 和 / 或 DirectorZone 服务。  如果您使用这些服务的任何功能，则必须同意相关的服务条款和隐私政策；这些内容可在以下链接找到： http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg、http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg、http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp 和 http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp 

* 软件授权合约
本 EULA 系用户 (用户) 与讯连科技股份有限公司 (以下简称"讯连科技") 之间达成的协议。当用户使用此讯连科技所有之软件(以下简称"本软件")，即表示用户接受本 EULA 的限制。

若用户同意接受本条款，请单击"是"。如果用户不同意本授权合约的条款，则请勿安装本软件，并请将它从计算机中移除。

* 授权范围和使用限制
以下是根据您拥有的许可证类型而特别制定的一般许可条款和使用限制。
讯连科技兹非专属性授权用户得在单一或特定数量 (视贵用户购买之授权数目而定) 之计算机上下载和 / 或安装所附 PowerDVD 软件，并在本授权合约的规定与限制下使用“本软件”。您同意并了解，您在使用软件时可接收软件更新、升级通知或任何商业电子信息。用户不可出租、转售、修改、变更、逆向编辑、解译或反解译"本软件"，或是创作"本软件"的衍生著作，亦不可移除"本软件"中所包含的任何著作权声明或信息。用户亦不可对“本软件”进行复制，除非是为备份用途制作一份拷贝。用户知道“本软件”授权于您而非出售给您。“本软件”必须从讯连科技或通过讯连科技授权的经销商合法取得，否则用户无权使用“本软件”。用户同意一旦“本软件”被运行、使用或安装，按相关法规，您不得将之转售或分发给任何他人或实体。您是否被合法允许转售“本软件”取决于您的居留地或受让人所在地的法律。一般而言，转售或分发将导致用户对“本软件”的使用许可自动终止。您承认并对使用、无法使用或安装不是从讯连科技、讯连科技的授权分销商或经销商购买或获得本软件的风险承担责任。请参见链接 [http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp]，以在讯连科技的官方网站上获得本软件的购买信息以及讯连科技授权经销商的信息。  
许可类型：
**个人消费者
如果您在个别许可下获得“本软件”，即表示该软件在上述一般条款下供您自己使用。
**站点许可
站点许可软件授权在单个地方使用。用户的最大数量受限于站点许可协议。
	**批量许可
每台设备只能安装一份。如果您是批量许可持有人，可进行多个备份并安装多套“本软件”。许可总份数将根据购买的数量而定。
**评估/试用许可
每台设备只能安装一份。“本软件”仅用于评估和/或试用目的。在此授予您的权利将在特定时间过后停止，“本软件”的使用有时间限制，过期后软件将被禁用。此许可非用于商业目的。
**订购许可
“本软件”的授权为订阅用途。您同意讯连科技可随时向您提供“本软件”的更改版本而对您不承担责任。继续访问订阅“软件”需要有效的 Internet 连接，在下载网站上可查看讯连科技收到的定期订阅付款以及订阅“软件”的使用和/或服务条款的协议。在此授予您的权利将在特定时间过后停止，“本软件”的使用有时间限制，过期后软件将被禁用。
**教育许可
“本软件”仅允许用于教育目的和非商业使用目的。可由学校、大学、学生及其法定监护人、学院、老师、教授、讲师和任何其他教育机构、学者或工作人员购买。  
如果您要出于商业目的使用“本软件”，则需以下其它未详尽罗列的第三方技术授权：
技术
合同名称
授权代理 / 授权方
       >BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA

讯连科技不对上述项目提供商业用途的授权，建议您按上述地址联系相关授权代理以了解更多信息。

*MPEG 分发
未获 MPEG-2 专利组合适用专利的授权 (该授权可在上述地址 MPEG-LA, LLC 中获取)，除符合套装媒体视频信息编码 MPEG-2 标准的个人用途外，都不得以任何方式使用本产品。
本产品有 AVC 专利组合授权，让消费者在个人和非商业用途中 (i) 对符合 AVC 标准 (“AVC 视频”) 的视频进行编码和 / 或 (ii) 对消费者在个人和非商业活动中编码的 AVC 视频和 / 或从授权提供 AVC 视频的视频提供者获得的视频进行解码。 对于任何其它用途不作授权或暗示授权。 其它信息可从 MPEG-LA 获得。
您还需确认未被授予或间接授予使用“本软件”来操作 MPEG-4 视频内容的权利，除非此 MPEG-4 内容已在“MPEG-4 基本要求”许可进行这种销售或提供的情况下，由内容销售商出售或提供给您。

* 权利归属
"本软件"之著作权及其它知识产权等相关权利或利益 (包括但不限于现已取得或未来可取得之著作权、专利权、商标权、营业秘密等) 皆为讯连科技所有。

* 升级
如果“本软件”为从旧版本的升级版，将根据许可更换方式提供。安装并使用“本软件”后，即表明您同意自愿终止先前的授权合约，并将不会继续使用旧版“软件”或将其转售和分发给他人或实体。

* 使用第三方授权的媒体内容
用户可以使用“本软件”中由第三方授权的图片、音频、视频、缩略图或其它媒体内容 (媒体内容)，以显示或完成藉由“本软件”所创作的作品，但是用户不得进行非法或违反诚实信用之使用，亦不可将其转而授权给任何第三方。 讯连科技对来自第三方的媒体内容不提供任何担保或陈述，并在法律允许的最大范围内不承担所有的责任。 

* 担保
讯连科技保证自用户购得"本软件"的九十 (90) 日内 (以下称"担保期间")，在一般正常的使用下，储存"本软件"之媒体无重大瑕疵。若媒体 (CD/DVD-ROM) 有任何瑕疵，讯连科技同意于担保期间内提供更换服务，但用户须将损坏的媒体连同发票退回讯连科技或供货商。如果讯连科技无法替换有缺陷的媒体，则讯连科技可自行选择或者是在用户终止本授权时全额退还购买金额，或者是用相同软件的新版本更换之。

"本软件"及其所附文件（包括使用说明）是按“现状”提供，不作任何类型的保证且非自动防故障。此外，讯连科技亦不对"本软件"或其文件之使用或使用结果之正确性及可靠性提供任何担保。"本软件"所产生的所有风险和性能表现的责任皆由用户承担。如因"本软件"或其文件之瑕疵而致用户受到损害，则用户必须自行负担所有修复或其它服务的费用，讯连科技或其经销商、配销商、代理商或员工不负担此责任或义务。

讯连科技亦不为其它明示或默示担保，其包括，但不限于，有关"本软件"之适销性、符合特定目的之使用、以及无侵害他人权利之情形。讯连科技不保证"本软件"之执行不会中断或完全无错误。即使讯连科技及其经销商、配销商、代理商或员工提出任何口头或书面之保证，亦不构成任何保证责任。 

讯连科技或其供应商对于用户因使用或无法使用"本软件"或者提供或无法提供支持服务所发生之任何直接、间接、随附或衍生性损害 (包括营业利益之损失、营业中断、营业资料之损失或其它金钱损失) 不负任何损害赔偿责任。

讯连科技对用户如有任何损害或赔偿责任，则以用户取得"本软件"之金额为责任上限。用户还同意赔偿并使讯连科技免受任何因您以非法目的使用本软件或违反本最终用户许可证协议，而导致的任何索赔、诉讼、损害、诉讼费和费用。

其它条款。于本"授权合约"终止时，用户应销毁"本软件"及其文件，以及所有现存的副本拷贝，并从硬盘或其它储存媒体中将"本软件"移除或删除。

本 EULA为用户与讯连科技之间的对"本软件"的完整理解，并以台湾地区法为准据法，且对于讯连科技及其继受人均适用。 

贵用户与讯连科技或其代理商、员工、继受者或让受人之间如有任何争议，无论是否因本 EULA而起，包括仲裁条款的合法性等，皆应以台湾台北为仲裁地，且受台湾地区仲裁法之规范。 

本授权合约翻译版本仅供参考。若翻译的版本与英文版本不一致，则以英文版本为准。

End User License Agreement ("EULA")
For PowerDVD

Date last modified: April 9, 2015.

Do not install or use the software until you have read and accepted all of the license terms. Permission to use the software is conditional upon your agreeing to the license terms. Installation or use of the software by you will be deemed to be acceptance of the license terms. Acceptance will bind you to the license terms in a legally enforceable contract with CyberLink Corp.

*CODEC ACTIVATION
When you use certain technologies essential to multi-media functions for the first time, the software application will collect the serial number of your computer system and the product key (CD key) for activation purposes only. 

*PRIVACY POLICY
Some of our products may send an anonymous event/signal to CyberLink’s backend server to collect information for the purpose of improving the end user experience, such as for example: 
-When user opts in or out of the CEIP (CyberLink Experience Improvement Program)/CPIP (CyberLink Product Improvement Program); and
-When our product is installed and/or uninstalled.

*RELATED SERVICES
Some of our product features may integrate with services such as MoovieLive and/or DirectorZone.  If you use any features from these services then you must agree to the terms of service and privacy policy thereof; which can be found at: http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg ; http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg ; http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp and http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp 

* SOFTWARE LICENSE AND LIMITED WARRANTY
This EULA is an agreement between you, the end user, and CyberLink Corp. ("CyberLink"). By using this software, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA.

If you agree to abide by these conditions, please click "Yes". IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS EULA, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SOFTWARE AND PROMPTLY REMOVE IT FROM YOUR COMPUTER.

* GRANT OF LICENSE & USAGE RESTRICTIONS
Below are the general license terms and usage restrictions followed by specific provisions depending on the type of license you have.
CyberLink, as licensor, grants to you, the licensee, a non-exclusive right to download and/or install the accompanying PowerDVD software program(s) (hereinafter the "SOFTWARE") on a certain number of computer(s)/ device(s) in accordance with the number of the license(s) you purchased and use the SOFTWARE in accordance with the terms contained in this license. You agree and acknowledge that you may receive SOFTWARE update, upgrade notices or any commercial electronic messages during the use of SOFTWARE. You shall not rent, lease, sublicense, modify, alter, reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile, or create any derivative work of the SOFTWARE, or remove any copyright notice or proprietary legend contained in the SOFTWARE. You shall not reproduce the SOFTWARE unless for backup purposes and limited to one copy only. You acknowledge this SOFTWARE is licensed to you, not sold to you. The SOFTWARE must be lawfully acquired from CyberLink or through CyberLink’s authorized resellers otherwise you do not have a right to use the SOFTWARE. You agree that once SOFTWARE is operated, used or installed; you may not resell or distribute it to another person or entity subject to the relevant statutes.  Whether you are legally allowed to resell the SOFTWARE will depend on the law of your place of residence or where the transferee is located.  Generally a resale or distribution will cause an automatic termination of your license to use the SOFTWARE. You own and are responsible for the risks of inability to use or install the SOFTWARE in purchasing or obtaining the SOFTWARE NOT from CyberLink, CyberLink’s authorized distributors or resellers or for used SOFTWARE.  Please refer to the link [http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp] for the SOFTWARE purchase information in CyberLink’s official website and for the information of CyberLink’s authorized distributors.  
License Types:
       **INDIVIDUAL CONSUMER
If you acquire the SOFTWARE under an individual license it is for your own use under the general terms above.
       **SITE LICENSE 
Site licensed SOFTWARE is licensed to be used in a single location.  The maximum number of users is limited by the site license agreement.
	**VOLUME LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed.  If you are the volume license holder then you may make multiple back-up copies and install multiple seats of the SOFTWARE. The total number of licensed copies will be limited to a capped number according to the purchased quantity in bulk.
       **EVALUATION/TRIAL LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed. The SOFTWARE is licensed for evaluation and/or trial purposes only. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled. This license is for non-commercial use.
       **SUBSCRIPTION LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for subscription purposes. You agree that CyberLink may change the version of the SOFTWARE provided to you at any time without liability to you. Ongoing access to Subscription SOFTWARE requires a working internet connection, CyberLink’s receipt of recurring subscription payments and agreement to the terms of use and/or service for Subscription SOFTWARE to be found on the downloading site. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled.
	**EDUCATIONAL LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for educational purposes and non-commercial use only. It may be purchased by schools, universities, students and their legal guardians, faculty, teachers, professors, lecturers and any other educational institutions, scholars or staff.  

If you are going to use the SOFTWARE for commercial purposes then additional licenses will be needed for the following non-exhaustive list of third party technologies:
>BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA


CyberLink does not license the above items for commercial use and you are advised to approach the relevant licensing agents at the above addresses for more information.

*MPEG DISTRIBUTION
ANY USE OF THIS PRODUCT IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN PERSONAL USE THAT COMPLIES WITH THE MPEG-2 STANDARD FOR ENCODING VIDEO INFORMATION FOR PACKAGED MEDIA IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED WITHOUT A LICENSE UNDER APPLICABLE PATENTS IN THE MPEG-2 PATENT PORTFOLIO, WHICH LICENSE IS AVAILABLE FROM MPEG-LA,LLC AT THE ADDRESS ABOVE.
THIS PRODUCT IS LICENSED UNDER THE AVC PATENT PORTFOLIO LICENSE FOR THE PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL USE OF A CONSUMER TO (i) ENCODE VIDEO IN COMLIANCE WITH THE AVC STANDARD (“AVC VIDEO”) AND/OR (ii) DECODE AVC VIDEO THAT WAS ENCODED BY A CONSUMER ENGAGED IN A PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY AND/OR WAS OBTAINED FROM A VIDEO PROVIDER LICENSED TO PROVIDE AVC VIDEO. NO LICENSE IS GRANTED OR SHALL BE IMPLIED FOR ANY OTHER USE. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM MPEG-LA.
You also acknowledge that no rights are granted or may be extended to you to use the SOFTWARE with MPEG-4 Video Content unless such MPEG-4 Content is sold or delivered to you by a content outlet licensed under the MPEG-4 Essential Claims to make such sale or delivery. 

* OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE
CyberLink retains the copyright, title and ownership of the SOFTWARE and the written materials ("Documentation") regardless of the form or media in or on which the original and other copies may exist.

* UPGRADES
If this copy of the SOFTWARE is an upgrade from an earlier version of the SOFTWARE, it is provided to you on a license exchange basis. Upon your installation and use of this copy of the SOFTWARE, you agree to voluntarily terminate your earlier EULA and you will not continue to use the earlier version of the SOFTWARE or resell or distribute it to another person or entity.

* USE OF MEDIA CONTENT LICENSED BY THIRD PARTIES
You may use pictures, audio, video, thumbnails or other media content (media content), if any, provided in the SOFTWARE, which may be licensed from third parties, to demonstrate or complete your work created by the use of the SOFTWARE; provided that you should not use the media content in any illegal, commercial or immoral manner, nor shall you grant your right to use to any third party. CyberLink does not provide any warranty or representation to these media content items from third parties and disclaims all liabilities to the maximum extent allowed by law.  

* LIMITED WARRANTY
CyberLink warrants the media on which the SOFTWARE is furnished to be free of defects in material and workmanship, under normal use, for a period of ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. If there is a defect in the media (CD/DVD-ROM), CyberLink's sole liability shall be to replace the defective media, which has been returned to CyberLink or the supplier with your dated invoice and is shown to be defective. In the event that CyberLink is unable to replace defective media, CyberLink shall at its sole discretion either refund your money upon your termination of this license or replace it with the newer version of the same software.

THIS SOFTWARE AND ACCOMPANYING DOCUMENTATION (INCLUDING INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE) ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND ARE NOT FAIL-SAFE. FURTHER, CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE, OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE, OF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IN TERMS OF CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CURRENTNESS, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE SOFTWARE IS ASSUMED BY YOU. IF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IS DEFECTIVE, YOU, AND NOT CYBERLINK OR ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS, OR EMPLOYEES, ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICE, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

CYBERLINK DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER IT IS MADE BY CYBERLINK, ON THIS CYBERLINK PRODUCT. CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY CYBERLINK, ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY OR IN ANY WAY INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THIS WARRANTY AND YOU MAY NOT RELY ON ANY SUCH INFORMATION OR ADVICE. 

NEITHER CYBERLINK NOR ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THIS PRODUCT SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE SUCH PRODUCT EVEN IF CYBERLINK HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Should any other warranties be found to exist, such warranties shall be limited in duration to ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. In no event will CyberLink's liability for any damages to you or any other person exceed the amount paid for the license to use the SOFTWARE.

You agree to bear the full, complete, and sole responsibility for using the SOFTWARE for any purpose. You also agree to indemnify and hold CyberLink harmless from any claims, proceedings, damages, costs, and expenses resulting from your use of the SOFTWARE for any illegal purpose or violation of this EULA.

Upon termination of this EULA, you should destroy the SOFTWARE and the Documentation and all the copies thereof and remove and delete the SOFTWARE from your hard disk or other storage device.

This EULA constitutes the entire agreement between you and CyberLink Corp. This EULA shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Taiwan and shall benefit CyberLink, its successors and assigns. 

Any claim or dispute between you and CyberLink or against any agent, employee, successor or assign of CyberLink, whether related to this EUL A or otherwise, and any claim or dispute related to this EULA or the relationship or duties contemplated under this EULA, including the validity of this arbitration clause, shall be resolved in Taipei, Taiwan, pursuant to the Taiwan Arbitration Act. 

This localized version of the EULA is for reference only. In case of inconsistencies between the localized version and the English version, the English version will prevail.