End User License Agreement （EULA）: 使用許諾契約書
PowerDVD 向け

最終更新日時:2015/04/09

当製品（以下「本ソフトウェア」という）の導入およびご利用の前に、以下の使用許諾契約書（以下「本契約書」とする）をお読みください。本ソフトウェアのご利用にあたっては、お客様が本契約書に記載された条項を事前に承諾いただくものとし、本ソフトウェアをインストール、バックアップ、ダウンロード、アクセス、または使用することによって、お客様は本契約書の条項に承諾されたものとします。本契約書は、本ソフトウェアに関してお客様（個人または法人のいずれであるかを問いません）とCyberLink Corp.（以下「サイバーリンク」といいます）との間に締結される法的な契約書となります。

*コーデックのアクティブ化
マルチメディア機能を使用する上で必須の特定技術を初めて使用する際は、本ソフトウェアはアクティブ化のみを目的として、お使いのコンピューター システムからシリアル番号と製品キー (CD キー) を収集します。 

*プライバシー ポリシー
弊社の一部の製品は、サイバーリンクのバックエンド サーバーに匿名イベント / 信号を送り、エンド ユーザーの使用感を向上させることを目的として、次の情報を収集します。 
- ユーザーが CEIP (CyberLink エクスペリエンス向上プログラム) / CPIP (CyberLink 製品向上プログラム) に参加または不参加する場合
- 弊社製品がインストールまたは削除されるとき

*関連サービス
弊社製品の一部の機能は、MoovieLive や DirectorZone などのサービスと統合されています。これらのサービスの機能を使用するには、サービス規約およびプライバシー ポリシーに同意していただく必要があります。詳しい内容は、次のリンクをご覧ください。http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg、http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg、http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp、http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp 

* ソフトウェア ライセンスおよび限定的保証
本契約書をお読みになり、記載された条項に承諾される場合は、導入画面中に表示される本契約の同意を求める画面で「はい」をクリックしてください。記載された条項に承諾いただけない場合は、インストール作業を中止し、本ソフトウェアの利用を中止するとともに、本ソフトウェアをコンピュータ上から削除してください。

* ライセンスの許諾および保証規定
基本的なライセンスの条件、およびお持ちのライセンスに含まれる条項に基づいて許諾される保証規定は、以下に記載するとおりです。
サイバーリンクは本ソフトウェアの非独占的な権利をお客様に対して許諾し、これによりお客様は、 PowerDVD ソフトウェアをご購入いただいたライセンス数に準じた台数のコンピュータへインストールし、本契約記載の条項に従って本ソフトウェアを利用することができるものとします。ソフトウェアをご使用中は、お客様の元にソフトウェア アップデート、アップグレードのお知らせ、広告が届けられることに同意していただきます。ソフトウェアを賃貸、貸与、販売、変更、修正、リバース エンジニアリング、逆アッセンブル、逆コンパイル、転用、あるいは商標の削除はできないものとします。バックアップを目的として本ソフトウェアの複製を作成する場合を除いて、本ソフトウェアはコピーできないものとします。本ソフトウェアはお客様に使用許諾されるものであり、販売されるものではありません。本ソフトウェアは、サイバーリンクまたはサイバーリンクが認可する再販業者を通じて合法的に取得されるものであり、さもなければ本ソフトウェアを使用する権利はないものとします。ソフトウェアをいったん操作、使用、インストールすると、文書および許諾契約に伴い他人または企業に再販できないものとします。本ソフトウェアの再販の合法性は、お客様または譲渡を受ける人の居住地の法律に拠ります。再販を行うと、本ソフトウェアのライセンスは自動的に解除されます。CyberLink、CyberLink の正規代理店、販売店、または使用済みソフトウェア以外から購入または取得したソフトウェアは、これを使用したり、インストールしたりすることができない可能性があります。このことをご理解の上で、お客様ご自身の判断と責任でかかるソフトウェアを使用またはインストールしてください。 ソフトウェアのご購入や CyberLink の正規代理店については、CyberLink の公式ホームページでこちら[http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp] をご覧ください。
ライセンスの種類:
**個人のお客様
ソフトウェアを単独ライセンスとして購入された場合は、上記の条件に基づいて個人的な目的にのみ使用するものとします。
**サイト ライセンス 
サイトライセンスは、ソフトウェアの単一組織での使用が許諾されます。許諾されるユーザー数は、サイトライセンス契約書に準じます。
**ボリューム ライセンス
デバイス 1 台につき、コピー 1 つをインストールできます。ボリューム ライセンスをお持ちの方は、バックアップ コピーを複数作成し、複数のデバイスにソフトウェアをインストールできます。許諾されるコピーの数は、購入されたライセンスの数に準じます。
**評価/体験版ライセンス
デバイス 1 台につき、コピー 1 つをインストールできます。ソフトウェアは、評価または体験的使用に限り使用が許諾されます。この場合、一定期間が経過し、一定の使用回数を超えると、お客様に許諾される権利は失われます。このライセンスを営利目的に使用することはできません。
**サブスクリプション ライセンス
本ソフトウェアは、サブスクリプションを目的として許諾されます。サイバーリンクは、お客様の許可を得ずにいつでも本ソフトウェアのバージョンを変更できるものとします。サブスクリプション ソフトウェアにアクセスするためには、インターネットに接続できること、サイバーリンクに対し定期的な支払が遂行されること、ダウンロードするサイトで使用およびサービス規約に同意していただくことが条件となります。この場合、一定期間が経過し、一定の使用回数を超えると、お客様に許諾される権利は失われます。
**教育ライセンス
本ソフトウェアは教育を目的として使用が許諾されるものであり、営利目的で使用することはできません。学校、大学、学生、保護者、学部、教師、教授、講師、その他の教育的施設、学者、職員が購入できます。  
本ソフトウェアを商用に用いる場合は、次の限定的な第三者の技術を使用するために追加ライセンスが必要です。
技術 	契約名	ライセンシング エージェント/ライセンサー
       >BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC - MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA

サイバーリンクは、商用を目的とした使用については上記の項目をライセンス許可しません。詳細は、上記のリンクから該当するライセンシング エージェントにお尋ねください。

*MPEG の配布
動画情報をパッケージ メディアにエンコードするために、MPEG-2 規格に準拠して個人的な目的に使用をする場合を除き、本製品をその他の目的に使用することは固くお断りします。ただし、「MPEG-2 PATENT PORTFOLIO」に基づいて当該特許に従いライセンスを取得してある場合はこの限りではありません。このライセンスは、上記リンクの MPEG-LA、LLC から取得できます。
本製品は、個人的な目的および非商用的な使用を目的として、「AVC PATENT PORTFOLIO LICENSE」に基づいた次の行為を許諾します。(i) AVC 規格 (「AVC ビデオ」) に基づいて動画をエンコードすること (ii) 個人的および非商用的使用においてエンコードされ、AVC ビデオの配布を許可されたビデオ プロバイダーから入手した AVC ビデオをデコードすること。これ以外の使用は認められません。詳しくは、MPEG-LA にお尋ねください。
MPEG-4 コンテンツが正式に販売されたものであること、または MPEG-4 Essential Claims のもとで許可されたコンテンツである場合を除き、本ソフトウェアで MPEG-4 ビデオ コンテンツを再生することはできません。

* 所有権
本ソフトウェアならびに関連印刷物の著作権、特許、商標権、ノウハウ及びその他のすべての知的所有権は、体裁、媒体、バックアップであるかの如何にかかわらず、その一切についてサイバーリンクに独占的に帰属します。本契約書に特に規定されていない権利はすべてサイバーリンクによって留保されます。

* アップグレード
古いバージョンからアップグレードしたソフトウェアは、ライセンス交換において提供されています。このコピーをインストールして使用すると、以前の使用許諾契約書は終了し、旧バージョンのソフトウェアを使用したり、他者または企業に再販したり、配布したりしないことに同意されたものとみなされます。

* サードパーティによりライセンスされたメディア コンテンツのご使用について
本ソフトウェア付属の画像、オーディオ、動画、サムネイル、その他のメディア コンテンツ (以下「メディア コンテンツ」とする) は、サードパーティから使用を許諾されており、ソフトウェアを使用して作業内容を説明したり、完了したりするために使用することができます。ただし、不法な、商用の、あるいは非道徳的なメディア コンテンツを使用したり、サードパーティから許可を得ていない画像を使用したりすることはできません。 サイバーリンクは、サードパーティが提供するかかるコンテンツ アイテムに対していかなる保証も代理も行いません。また、法律で認められる範囲において、いかなる責任も負いません。

* 保証及び責任の限定
本ソフトウェアおよび付属資料 (使用説明書を含む) は、「現状のまま」一切の保証なしで提供されています。 サイバーリンクは、本ソフトウェア、関連印刷物、およびサポートサービスに起因してお客様又はその他の第三者に生じた結果的損害、付随的損害及び逸失利益に関して、一切の瑕疵担保責任および保証責任を負いません。また、本ソフトウェア又は関連印刷物の物理的な紛失、盗難、事故及び誤用等に起因するお客様の損害につき一切の保証をいたしません。
サイバーリンクは、本契約書に違反する目的でソフトウェアを使用することで生じるいかなるクレーム、訴訟、損害賠償、訴訟費用、経費に関して、一切の責任を負いません。
サイバーリンクは、本ソフトウェア及び関連印刷物の機能もしくはサポートサービスがお客様の特定の目的に適合することを保証するものではなく、本ソフトウェアの選択、導入、使用、およびそれによって得られる結果については、すべてお客様の責任となります。

本契約書に記載のない保証条項が発見された場合、保証対象期間はお客様が本ソフトウェアを購入された日から９０日以内とし、保証金額はお客様が本ソフトウェアの購入のためにお支払いいただいた金額を超えないものとします。
お客様が本契約を解除する場合、本ソフトウェアおよび関連印刷物のバックアップを含む一切を、物理的および電子的に読み取りできない状態で破棄するとともに、コンピュータ上の本ソフトウェアおよび関連印刷物の一切を消去するものとします。

本契約は、本ソフトウェアに関してお客様とサイバーリンクとの間に締結され、台湾における法律に準拠します。本契約に起因する紛争の解決については、Taiwan Arbitration Act. に準ずるものとします。

本日本語訳は参照用であり、英文契約書の理解の補助のために作成されたものです。記載の内容に差異がある場合は英文の契約書：End User License Agreement （'EULA'）が優先されます。 

End User License Agreement ("EULA")
For PowerDVD

Date last modified: April 9, 2015.

Do not install or use the software until you have read and accepted all of the license terms. Permission to use the software is conditional upon your agreeing to the license terms. Installation or use of the software by you will be deemed to be acceptance of the license terms. Acceptance will bind you to the license terms in a legally enforceable contract with CyberLink Corp.

*CODEC ACTIVATION
When you use certain technologies essential to multi-media functions for the first time, the software application will collect the serial number of your computer system and the product key (CD key) for activation purposes only. 

*PRIVACY POLICY
Some of our products may send an anonymous event/signal to CyberLink’s backend server to collect information for the purpose of improving the end user experience, such as for example: 
-When user opts in or out of the CEIP (CyberLink Experience Improvement Program)/CPIP (CyberLink Product Improvement Program); and
-When our product is installed and/or uninstalled.

*RELATED SERVICES
Some of our product features may integrate with services such as MoovieLive and/or DirectorZone.  If you use any features from these services then you must agree to the terms of service and privacy policy thereof; which can be found at: http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg ; http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg ; http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp and http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp 

* SOFTWARE LICENSE AND LIMITED WARRANTY
This EULA is an agreement between you, the end user, and CyberLink Corp. ("CyberLink"). By using this software, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA.

If you agree to abide by these conditions, please click "Yes". IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS EULA, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SOFTWARE AND PROMPTLY REMOVE IT FROM YOUR COMPUTER.

* GRANT OF LICENSE & USAGE RESTRICTIONS
Below are the general license terms and usage restrictions followed by specific provisions depending on the type of license you have.
CyberLink, as licensor, grants to you, the licensee, a non-exclusive right to download and/or install the accompanying PowerDVD software program(s) (hereinafter the "SOFTWARE") on a certain number of computer(s)/ device(s) in accordance with the number of the license(s) you purchased and use the SOFTWARE in accordance with the terms contained in this license. You agree and acknowledge that you may receive SOFTWARE update, upgrade notices or any commercial electronic messages during the use of SOFTWARE. You shall not rent, lease, sublicense, modify, alter, reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile, or create any derivative work of the SOFTWARE, or remove any copyright notice or proprietary legend contained in the SOFTWARE. You shall not reproduce the SOFTWARE unless for backup purposes and limited to one copy only. You acknowledge this SOFTWARE is licensed to you, not sold to you. The SOFTWARE must be lawfully acquired from CyberLink or through CyberLink’s authorized resellers otherwise you do not have a right to use the SOFTWARE. You agree that once SOFTWARE is operated, used or installed; you may not resell or distribute it to another person or entity subject to the relevant statutes.  Whether you are legally allowed to resell the SOFTWARE will depend on the law of your place of residence or where the transferee is located.  Generally a resale or distribution will cause an automatic termination of your license to use the SOFTWARE. You own and are responsible for the risks of inability to use or install the SOFTWARE in purchasing or obtaining the SOFTWARE NOT from CyberLink, CyberLink’s authorized distributors or resellers or for used SOFTWARE.  Please refer to the link [http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp] for the SOFTWARE purchase information in CyberLink’s official website and for the information of CyberLink’s authorized distributors.  
License Types:
       **INDIVIDUAL CONSUMER
If you acquire the SOFTWARE under an individual license it is for your own use under the general terms above.
       **SITE LICENSE 
Site licensed SOFTWARE is licensed to be used in a single location.  The maximum number of users is limited by the site license agreement.
	**VOLUME LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed.  If you are the volume license holder then you may make multiple back-up copies and install multiple seats of the SOFTWARE. The total number of licensed copies will be limited to a capped number according to the purchased quantity in bulk.
       **EVALUATION/TRIAL LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed. The SOFTWARE is licensed for evaluation and/or trial purposes only. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled. This license is for non-commercial use.
       **SUBSCRIPTION LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for subscription purposes. You agree that CyberLink may change the version of the SOFTWARE provided to you at any time without liability to you. Ongoing access to Subscription SOFTWARE requires a working internet connection, CyberLink’s receipt of recurring subscription payments and agreement to the terms of use and/or service for Subscription SOFTWARE to be found on the downloading site. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled.
	**EDUCATIONAL LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for educational purposes and non-commercial use only. It may be purchased by schools, universities, students and their legal guardians, faculty, teachers, professors, lecturers and any other educational institutions, scholars or staff.  

If you are going to use the SOFTWARE for commercial purposes then additional licenses will be needed for the following non-exhaustive list of third party technologies:
>BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA


CyberLink does not license the above items for commercial use and you are advised to approach the relevant licensing agents at the above addresses for more information.

*MPEG DISTRIBUTION
ANY USE OF THIS PRODUCT IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN PERSONAL USE THAT COMPLIES WITH THE MPEG-2 STANDARD FOR ENCODING VIDEO INFORMATION FOR PACKAGED MEDIA IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED WITHOUT A LICENSE UNDER APPLICABLE PATENTS IN THE MPEG-2 PATENT PORTFOLIO, WHICH LICENSE IS AVAILABLE FROM MPEG-LA,LLC AT THE ADDRESS ABOVE.
THIS PRODUCT IS LICENSED UNDER THE AVC PATENT PORTFOLIO LICENSE FOR THE PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL USE OF A CONSUMER TO (i) ENCODE VIDEO IN COMLIANCE WITH THE AVC STANDARD (“AVC VIDEO”) AND/OR (ii) DECODE AVC VIDEO THAT WAS ENCODED BY A CONSUMER ENGAGED IN A PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY AND/OR WAS OBTAINED FROM A VIDEO PROVIDER LICENSED TO PROVIDE AVC VIDEO. NO LICENSE IS GRANTED OR SHALL BE IMPLIED FOR ANY OTHER USE. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM MPEG-LA.
You also acknowledge that no rights are granted or may be extended to you to use the SOFTWARE with MPEG-4 Video Content unless such MPEG-4 Content is sold or delivered to you by a content outlet licensed under the MPEG-4 Essential Claims to make such sale or delivery. 

* OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE
CyberLink retains the copyright, title and ownership of the SOFTWARE and the written materials ("Documentation") regardless of the form or media in or on which the original and other copies may exist.

* UPGRADES
If this copy of the SOFTWARE is an upgrade from an earlier version of the SOFTWARE, it is provided to you on a license exchange basis. Upon your installation and use of this copy of the SOFTWARE, you agree to voluntarily terminate your earlier EULA and you will not continue to use the earlier version of the SOFTWARE or resell or distribute it to another person or entity.

* USE OF MEDIA CONTENT LICENSED BY THIRD PARTIES
You may use pictures, audio, video, thumbnails or other media content (media content), if any, provided in the SOFTWARE, which may be licensed from third parties, to demonstrate or complete your work created by the use of the SOFTWARE; provided that you should not use the media content in any illegal, commercial or immoral manner, nor shall you grant your right to use to any third party. CyberLink does not provide any warranty or representation to these media content items from third parties and disclaims all liabilities to the maximum extent allowed by law.  

* LIMITED WARRANTY
CyberLink warrants the media on which the SOFTWARE is furnished to be free of defects in material and workmanship, under normal use, for a period of ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. If there is a defect in the media (CD/DVD-ROM), CyberLink's sole liability shall be to replace the defective media, which has been returned to CyberLink or the supplier with your dated invoice and is shown to be defective. In the event that CyberLink is unable to replace defective media, CyberLink shall at its sole discretion either refund your money upon your termination of this license or replace it with the newer version of the same software.

THIS SOFTWARE AND ACCOMPANYING DOCUMENTATION (INCLUDING INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE) ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND ARE NOT FAIL-SAFE. FURTHER, CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE, OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE, OF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IN TERMS OF CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CURRENTNESS, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE SOFTWARE IS ASSUMED BY YOU. IF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IS DEFECTIVE, YOU, AND NOT CYBERLINK OR ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS, OR EMPLOYEES, ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICE, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

CYBERLINK DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER IT IS MADE BY CYBERLINK, ON THIS CYBERLINK PRODUCT. CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY CYBERLINK, ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY OR IN ANY WAY INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THIS WARRANTY AND YOU MAY NOT RELY ON ANY SUCH INFORMATION OR ADVICE. 

NEITHER CYBERLINK NOR ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THIS PRODUCT SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE SUCH PRODUCT EVEN IF CYBERLINK HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Should any other warranties be found to exist, such warranties shall be limited in duration to ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. In no event will CyberLink's liability for any damages to you or any other person exceed the amount paid for the license to use the SOFTWARE.

You agree to bear the full, complete, and sole responsibility for using the SOFTWARE for any purpose. You also agree to indemnify and hold CyberLink harmless from any claims, proceedings, damages, costs, and expenses resulting from your use of the SOFTWARE for any illegal purpose or violation of this EULA.

Upon termination of this EULA, you should destroy the SOFTWARE and the Documentation and all the copies thereof and remove and delete the SOFTWARE from your hard disk or other storage device.

This EULA constitutes the entire agreement between you and CyberLink Corp. This EULA shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Taiwan and shall benefit CyberLink, its successors and assigns. 

Any claim or dispute between you and CyberLink or against any agent, employee, successor or assign of CyberLink, whether related to this EUL A or otherwise, and any claim or dispute related to this EULA or the relationship or duties contemplated under this EULA, including the validity of this arbitration clause, shall be resolved in Taipei, Taiwan, pursuant to the Taiwan Arbitration Act. 

This localized version of the EULA is for reference only. In case of inconsistencies between the localized version and the English version, the English version will prevail.