사용자 계약서 ("EULA")
PowerDVD 용

마지막 수정 날짜: 2015년 4월 9일

모든 라이센스 조항을 읽고 수락할 때까지는 소프트웨어를 설치하거나 사용하지 마십시오. 이 소프트웨어에 대한 사용 허가는 이 라이센스 조항에 대한 귀하의 동의를 조건으로 하고 있습니다. 귀하가 이 소프트웨어를 설치 및 사용하는 것은 이 라이센스 조항을 수락한 것으로 간주하게 됩니다 수락이라 함은 귀하가 이 라이센스 조항에 대해 사이버링크와 법적 효력이 있는 계약을 맺게 되는 것입니다.

*코덱 활성화
멀티미디어 기능에 필수적인 특정 기술을 처음으로 사용할 때, 소프트웨어 응용 프로그램은 활성화 목적으로만 귀하의 컴퓨터 시스템의 일련 번호와 제품 키(CD 키)를 수집합니다. 

*개인 정보 보호 정책
당사 제품 중 일부는 다음 예와 같은 경우 사용자 경험을 개선하기 위한 목적으로 익명 이벤트/신호를 CyberLink의 백엔드 서버로 전송하여 정보를 수집할 수 있습니다. 
-사용자가 CEIP(CyberLink 경험 개선 프로그램)/CPIP (CyberLink 제품 개선 프로그램)에 들어가거나 나갈 때
-당사 제품을 설치 및/또는 제거할 때

*관련 서비스
당사 제품 기능 중 일부는 MoovieLive 및/또는 DirectorZone 같은 서비스와 통합되어 있을 수 있습니다.  이러한 서비스에서 제공하는 기능을 사용할 경우 다음 위치에 있는 서비스 약관 및 개인 정보 보호 정책에 동의해야 합니다. http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg ; http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg ; http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp 및 http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp  

* 소프트웨어 라이센스 및 한정 보증 
이것은 최종사용자인 귀하와 사이버링크간의 계약서입니다. 본 소프트웨어를 사용하는 것에 의해, 귀하는 이 계약서의 조항에 의한 의무를 지게 되는 것에 동의하는 것입니다

만일 귀하가 이들 조항을 준수하는 것에 동의한다면, "Yes(예)"에 클릭 하십시오. 만일 인증서 내용에 동의 하지 않는다면 이 소프트웨어를 사용하지말고 즉시 삭제하십시요.

* 라이센스의 허가 및 사용 제한
아래에는 일반 라이센스 조항과 사용 제한 사항 및 귀하가 소유한 라이센스 유형에 따라 다른 구체적인 규정이 있습니다.
CyberLink는 라이센스 허가자로서, 라이센스를 소지한 사용자에게 함께 제공되는 PowerDVD 소프트웨어 프로그램(이후 "소프트웨어")을 구입한 라이센스 수에 해당하는 컴퓨터/장치에 다운로드 및/또는 설치한 후 이 라이센스에 포함된 약관에 부합되게 사용할 수 있는 비독점 권한을 승인합니다. 귀하는 소프트웨어를 사용하는 동안 소프트웨어 업데이트, 업그레이드 알림, 또는 전자적인 상업 메시지를 수신하게 될 수 있다는 것에 동의하고 인정합니다. 소프트웨어를 임대, 대여, 라이센스 재허여, 수정, 변경, 리버스 엔지니어링, 디스어셈블, 디컴파일하거나, 소프트웨어의 파생물을 작성하거나, 소프트웨어에 포함된 저작권 고지 또는 독점적인 범례를 제거할 수 없습니다. 소프트웨어는 1개의 백업용 사본을 제외하고 복제할 수 없습니다. 귀하는 이 소프트웨어가 귀하에게 판매된 것이 아니라 라이센스가 부여된 것임을 인정합니다. 이 소프트웨어는 CyberLink 또는 CyberLink의 공인 판매업체를 통해 합법적으로 취득해야 하며, 그렇지 않으면 이 소프트웨어를 사용할 권한이 없습니다. 귀하는 일단 소프트웨어를 작동, 사용 또는 설치한 후에는 관련 법규에 따라 다른 사람이나 독립체에 소프트웨어를 재판매 또는 배포하지 않을 것에 동의합니다.  귀하의 소프트웨어 재판매가 법률적으로 허용되는지 여부는 귀하의 거주 지역 법률 또는 양수인이 있는 지역의 법률에 따릅니다.  일반적으로 재판매 또는 배포하는 경우 이 소프트웨어 사용에 대한 라이센스가 자동으로 해지됩니다. CyberLink, CyberLink의 공인 판매처 또는 리셀러로부터 구입하거나 획득하지 않은 소프트웨어 또는 중고 소프트웨어인 경우, 이를 사용하거나 설치하는 하는 데 따른 작동 불능의 위험은 전적으로 사용자가 책임을 집니다. 링크 [http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp]를 방문하여 CyberLink의 공식 웹사이트에서 소프트웨어를 구매하는 방법과 CyberLink의 공인 판매처에 관한 정보를 참조하십시오.
라이센스 유형:
**개인 소비자
개인 라이센스 하에서 소프트웨어를 획득한 경우 라이센스는 위에 나온 일반 약관에 따라 귀하 자신의 사용을 위한 것입니다.
**사이트 라이센스 
사이트 라이센스 소프트웨어는 단일 위치에서 사용하도록 라이센스가 부여됩니다.  최대 사용자 수는 사이트 라이센스 계약에 의해 제한됩니다.
**볼륨 라이센스
장치당 한 개의 사본만 설치할 수 있습니다.  볼륨 라이센스 소유자인 경우에는 소프트웨어의 여러 백업 사본을 만들어 여러 자리에 설치할 수 있습니다. 라이센스가 부여된 사본의 총 수는 대량 구매 수량에 의해 제한됩니다.
**평가/시험판 라이센스
장치당 한 개의 사본만 설치할 수 있습니다. 소프트웨어는 평가 및/또는 시험 사용 목적으로만 라이센스가 부여됩니다. 여기에서 귀하에게 부여된 권리는 명시된 기간이 지난 후 중지되며 소프트웨어 사용에는 시간이 제한됩니다. 그 시간 후에는 소프트웨어를 사용하지 못할 수 있습니다. 이 라이센스는 비상업적 용도입니다.
**구독 라이센스
소프트웨어는 구독 목적으로 라이센스가 부여됩니다. 귀하는 귀하에게 제공된 버전의 소프트웨어를 CyberLink가 언제든지 자유롭게 변경할 수 있다는 것에 동의합니다. 구독 소프트웨어에 액세스하기 위해서는 작동하는 인터넷 연결이 필요하고, 발생한 구독료 지불을 CyberLink가 수령해야 하며, 다운로드 사이트에 있는 구독 소프트웨어의 사용 및 서비스 약관에 동의해야 합니다. 여기에서 귀하에게 부여된 권리는 명시된 기간이 지난 후 중지되며 소프트웨어 사용에는 시간이 제한됩니다. 그 시간 후에는 소프트웨어를 사용하지 못할 수 있습니다.
**교육 라이센스
소프트웨어는 교육 목적 및 비상업적 용도로만 라이센스가 부여됩니다. 이 소프트웨어는 학교, 대학교, 학생 및 법정 후견인, 교수, 교사, 강사 및 그 외 교육 기관, 장학생 및 직원이 구매할 수 있습니다.  
소프트웨어를 상업 목적에 사용하려는 경우에는 다음 비정성적 목록에 나온 제3자 기술에 대해 소프트웨어를 상업 목적에 사용하려는 경우에는 다음 정성적 목록에 나온 제3자 기술에 대해 추가 라이센스가 필요합니다.
기술 	계약 이름 	라이센스 에이전트/ 라이센스 허가자
       >BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC - MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA

CyberLink는 위 항목에 대해 상업적 목적으로 라이센스를 허가하지 않으며, 추가 정보가 필요하면 위에 나온 주소로 귀하가 관련 라이센스 에이전트에 연락하십시오.

*MPEG 배포
MPEG-2 특허 포트폴리오의 해당 특허법 하에서 라이센스를 허가받지 않고 패키지된 미디어에 대한 비디오 정보 인코딩을 위해 MPEG-2 표준을 따르는 개인 용도 외에 다른 방식으로 이 제품을 사용하는 것은 명시적으로 금지됩니다. 해당 라이센스는 위 주소의 MPEG-LA, LLC로부터 구할 수 있습니다.
이 제품은 AVC 특허 포트폴리오 라이센스 하에서 개인적이고 비상업적인 용도로 소비자에게 다음 작업을 할 수 있도록 허가되었습니다. (i) AVC 표준을 따르는 비디오의 인코딩(“AVC 비디오”) 및/또는 (ii) 개인적이고 비상업적인 활동에 관련되어 소비자가 인코딩한 AVC 비디오 및/또는 AVC 비디오 공급을 허가받은 비디오 공급업체로부터 얻은 AVC 비디오의 디코딩. 그 밖의 용도로는 라이센스가 허용되지 않으며 그렇게 해석되어서도 안 됩니다. 추가 정보는 MPEG-LA로부터 얻을 수 있습니다.

또한 귀하는 이 소프트웨어로 이용하려는 MPEG-4 비디오 컨텐트에 대해 해당 MPEG-4 컨텐트가 MPEG-4 Essential Claims의 규정에 따라 판매 또는 유통에 준하는 판매 경로를 통해 판매 또는 제공된 경우가 아니라면 이 소프트웨어를 해당 컨텐트와 함께 사용할 권리가 허여되지 않습니다.

* 소프트웨어의 소유권 
사이버링크는 본 소프트웨어의 저작권, 타이틀 및 소유권과 원본 또는 다른 카피가 존재 할 수 있는 형태 또는 매체에 관계없이 문서로 된 자료(증명서)를 보유하고 있습니다 

* 업그레이드. 
이 소프트웨어가 동일한 소프트웨어의 이전 버전에서 업그레이드한 사본인 경우 라이센스 교환 기반으로 제공됩니다. 이 소프트웨어 사본을 설치하고 사용하는 것은 이전 EULA를 해지하고 이 소프트웨어의 이전 버전을 계속 사용하지 않거나 다른 사람 또는 독립체에게 재판매 또는 배포하지 않을 것에 자발적으로 동의하는 것입니다.

* 제3자에 의해 라이센스된 미디어 컨텐트의 이용
귀하는 본 소프트웨어를 사용함으로써 만들어지는 귀하의 작업을 설명 또는 완료하기 위해, 제3자로부터 라이센스될 수도 있는 본 소프트웨어에 제공된 사진, 오디오, 비디오, 썸네일 또는 기타 미디터 컨텐트(미디어 컨텐트)를 귀하가 불법적 또는 비도덕적 방식으로 사용하지 않고 그 사용 권한을 제3자에게 허가하지 않는다는 것을 조건으로 하여 이용할 수 있습니다. CyberLink는 이러한 제3자의 미디어 컨텐트 항목를 보증하거나 대리하지 않으며 법률이 허용하는 최대 한도까지 책임을 부인합니다.  

* 제한적 보증. 
사이버링크는 본 소프트웨어가 귀하에 인도된 날로부터 90일 동안 정상적인 사용중에 본 소프트웨어가 제공된 매체가 재질 및 기능에 있어 결함이 없다는 것을 보증합니다 만일 매체에 결함이 있으면, 사이버링크의 단독 책임 하에 날짜가 적힌 송장과 함께 결함이 있는 매체 (CD/DVD-ROM) 를 사이버링크 또는 공급자에게 반송하면 교환해드리겠습니다. 사이버링크사가 손상된 CD를 교환해 줄수 없는경우에 ,사이버링크사는 귀하가 라이센스를 끝내는조건으로 현금으로 보상하거나동일 소프트웨어의 최신판으로 교환해 줄수 있습니다.

이 소프트웨어 및 동봉된 문서(사용 지침 포함)는 어떠한 유형의 보증 및 고장에 대한 안전 장치 없이 "있는 그대로" 제공됩니다.　또한, 사이버링크는 정확성, 정밀성, 신뢰성, 시사성 또는 다른 점에 있어서 본 소프트웨어의 사용 또는 사용 결과에 관해 보증하거나 보장하거나 또는 어떠한 대리도 하지 않습니다 . 본 소프트웨어의 성능 및 결과에 관한 전체적인 리스크는 귀하에게 잇습니다 . 만일 소프트웨어 및 서류에 결함이 있으면, 사이버링크 또는 그의 딜러, 배급자, 대리점 또는 피고용인이 아니라, 귀하가 모든 필요한 서비스, 수리 또는 교정에 관한 비용을 책임집니다. 

사이버링크는 이 사이버링크 제품에 대해 상품성, 특정 목적에 대한 적합성 및 비침해성(사이버링크에 제조된 것인지 여부에 관계없음)에 관한 묵시적 보증을 포함하여(이들에 국한되는 것은 아님) 명시적 또는 묵시적인 모든 다른 보증을 배제합니다. 사이버링크는 본 소프트웨어가 일시적으로 중단되는 일이 없거나 오류가 없다는 것을 보증하지 않습니다 . 사이버링크와 그의 딜러, 대리점, 에이전트 또는 피고용인에 의해 제공되는 구두 또는 문서로 된 정보나 권고가 보증을 의미하는 것이 아니며, 어떤 방식으로든 보증 범위의 확대를 의미하는 것이 아니며, 귀하는 이러한 정보 또는 권고에 의존하지 않을 수 있습니다. 

 사이버링크 또는 본 제품의 창작, 생산 또는 배달에 관여된 다른 누구라도 본 제품의 사용 또는 사용 불능으로 부터 발생되는 어떠한 직접적이거나 간접적이거나 결과적이거나 또는 우발적인 손해(사업상 이익의 손실, 사업 방해, 데이터의 손실, 사업정보의 손실 또는 다른 금전상의 손실에 대한 손해를 포함함)에 대해 책임을 지지 않으며, 사이버링크가 이러한 손해의 가능성에 관해 통지를 받았던 경우에도 책임을 지지 않습니다 .

어떤 다른 보증이 존재하는 것을 알게 되는 경우에, 이러한 보증은 본 제품이 귀하에게 인도된 날로부터 90일로 제한됩니다 . 귀하 또는 다른 사람의 어떤 손해에 대한 사이버링크의 책임은 본 소프트웨어를 사용하기 위한 라이센스를 위해 지불된 금액을 초과하지 않습니다.

사용자는 소프트웨어 사용에 관한 완전한 독자적인 책임을 진다는것에 동의 합니다 . 또한 귀하는 불법적인 목적 또는 이 EULA를 위반한 사용에 따른 배상과 클레임과 손해 그 비용 일체에 대해 사이버링크에 무해하게 할것에 동의 합니다.

본 계약서의 종료시, 귀하는 본 소프트웨어 및 증명서와 모든 복사본을 파기해야 하며, 귀하의 하드-디스크나 또는 다른 기억장치로부터 본 소프트웨어를 제거해야 합니다

본 계약서는 귀하와 사이버링크간의 전체 계약을 규정합니다. 본 계약서는 대만의 법률에 따라 의미가 결정되고 해석 되어야 하며, 사이버링크 및 그 상속자와 양수인에게 이익이 되어야 합니다. 

귀하와 사이버링크간의 어떠한 배상청구 또는 분쟁, 사이버링크의 대리점, 피고용인, 상속자 또는 양수인(본 계약서와 관련되어 있는지 여부와 관계없음)에 대한 배상청구 또는 분쟁 및 본 중재조항의 합법성을 포함하여 본 계약서 또는 본 계약서 하에서 예상되는 관계나 의무와 관련된 어떠한 배상청구 또는 분쟁도 대만의 중재법 조항에 따라 대만의 타이페이에서 해결되어야 합니다 . 

EULA의 본 한국어 버전은 참조용입니다 . 한국어 버전과 영문 버전 사이에 불일치가 존재 하는 경우에, 영문 버전이 우선합니다 .

End User License Agreement ("EULA")
For PowerDVD

Date last modified: April 9, 2015.

Do not install or use the software until you have read and accepted all of the license terms. Permission to use the software is conditional upon your agreeing to the license terms. Installation or use of the software by you will be deemed to be acceptance of the license terms. Acceptance will bind you to the license terms in a legally enforceable contract with CyberLink Corp.

*CODEC ACTIVATION
When you use certain technologies essential to multi-media functions for the first time, the software application will collect the serial number of your computer system and the product key (CD key) for activation purposes only. 

*PRIVACY POLICY
Some of our products may send an anonymous event/signal to CyberLink’s backend server to collect information for the purpose of improving the end user experience, such as for example: 
-When user opts in or out of the CEIP (CyberLink Experience Improvement Program)/CPIP (CyberLink Product Improvement Program); and
-When our product is installed and/or uninstalled.

*RELATED SERVICES
Some of our product features may integrate with services such as MoovieLive and/or DirectorZone.  If you use any features from these services then you must agree to the terms of service and privacy policy thereof; which can be found at: http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/term_of_use.mlg ; http://www.moovielive.com/index/pages/privacy.mlg ; http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/termsOfService.jsp and http://directorzone.cyberlink.com/info/privacy.jsp 

* SOFTWARE LICENSE AND LIMITED WARRANTY
This EULA is an agreement between you, the end user, and CyberLink Corp. ("CyberLink"). By using this software, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA.

If you agree to abide by these conditions, please click "Yes". IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS EULA, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SOFTWARE AND PROMPTLY REMOVE IT FROM YOUR COMPUTER.

* GRANT OF LICENSE & USAGE RESTRICTIONS
Below are the general license terms and usage restrictions followed by specific provisions depending on the type of license you have.
CyberLink, as licensor, grants to you, the licensee, a non-exclusive right to download and/or install the accompanying PowerDVD software program(s) (hereinafter the "SOFTWARE") on a certain number of computer(s)/ device(s) in accordance with the number of the license(s) you purchased and use the SOFTWARE in accordance with the terms contained in this license. You agree and acknowledge that you may receive SOFTWARE update, upgrade notices or any commercial electronic messages during the use of SOFTWARE. You shall not rent, lease, sublicense, modify, alter, reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile, or create any derivative work of the SOFTWARE, or remove any copyright notice or proprietary legend contained in the SOFTWARE. You shall not reproduce the SOFTWARE unless for backup purposes and limited to one copy only. You acknowledge this SOFTWARE is licensed to you, not sold to you. The SOFTWARE must be lawfully acquired from CyberLink or through CyberLink’s authorized resellers otherwise you do not have a right to use the SOFTWARE. You agree that once SOFTWARE is operated, used or installed; you may not resell or distribute it to another person or entity subject to the relevant statutes.  Whether you are legally allowed to resell the SOFTWARE will depend on the law of your place of residence or where the transferee is located.  Generally a resale or distribution will cause an automatic termination of your license to use the SOFTWARE. You own and are responsible for the risks of inability to use or install the SOFTWARE in purchasing or obtaining the SOFTWARE NOT from CyberLink, CyberLink’s authorized distributors or resellers or for used SOFTWARE.  Please refer to the link [http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/regional-stores/enu/index.jsp] for the SOFTWARE purchase information in CyberLink’s official website and for the information of CyberLink’s authorized distributors.  
License Types:
       **INDIVIDUAL CONSUMER
If you acquire the SOFTWARE under an individual license it is for your own use under the general terms above.
       **SITE LICENSE 
Site licensed SOFTWARE is licensed to be used in a single location.  The maximum number of users is limited by the site license agreement.
	**VOLUME LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed.  If you are the volume license holder then you may make multiple back-up copies and install multiple seats of the SOFTWARE. The total number of licensed copies will be limited to a capped number according to the purchased quantity in bulk.
       **EVALUATION/TRIAL LICENSE
Only one copy per device may be installed. The SOFTWARE is licensed for evaluation and/or trial purposes only. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled. This license is for non-commercial use.
       **SUBSCRIPTION LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for subscription purposes. You agree that CyberLink may change the version of the SOFTWARE provided to you at any time without liability to you. Ongoing access to Subscription SOFTWARE requires a working internet connection, CyberLink’s receipt of recurring subscription payments and agreement to the terms of use and/or service for Subscription SOFTWARE to be found on the downloading site. The rights granted to you herein will cease after a specified time period and the SOFTWARE usage is time limited, after expiration of which it may be disabled.
	**EDUCATIONAL LICENSE
The SOFTWARE is licensed for educational purposes and non-commercial use only. It may be purchased by schools, universities, students and their legal guardians, faculty, teachers, professors, lecturers and any other educational institutions, scholars or staff.  

If you are going to use the SOFTWARE for commercial purposes then additional licenses will be needed for the following non-exhaustive list of third party technologies:
>BD-3D -Blu-ray Disc Read Only Format 3.0 and Logo License Agreement
Contact: Blu-Ray Disc Association, 10 Universal City Plaza, T-100, Universal
City, CA 91608, USA
       >BD-J - Oracle Community Source License
Contact: Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway 15F, #100, Redwood Shores, California 94065, USA
       >DivX Decoder - Software License Agreement
Contact: Rovi Guides, Inc., Credit Dept. 7140 Lewis Avenue, Tulsa, OK 74136, USA
       >H.264/MPEG-4 AVC - AVC Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-1/2 Audio (Encoder) - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MPEG-2 Video - MPEG-2 Patent Portfolio License
       >MVC – MVC Patent Portfolio License
       > VC-1 Decoder - VC-1 Patent Portfolio License
       > H.265/MPEG HEVC - TBA
Contact: MPEG-LA, LLC, 6312 S. Fiddlers Green Circle, Suite 400E Greenwood Village, Colorado, USA 80111
       > Sensio 3D/2D - Software Library License and Ancillary Services Agreement
Contact: Sensio Technologies, Inc., 1751, Richardson, Suite 4.206, Montreal (Quebec), Canada, H3K 1G6
       > MPEG-2/4 AAC, 5.1-ch Decoder + 2-ch Encoder - AAC Patent License Agreement
Contact: Via Licensing Corporation, 475 Brannan Street, Suite 320
San Francisco, CA 94107-5420, USA


CyberLink does not license the above items for commercial use and you are advised to approach the relevant licensing agents at the above addresses for more information.

*MPEG DISTRIBUTION
ANY USE OF THIS PRODUCT IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN PERSONAL USE THAT COMPLIES WITH THE MPEG-2 STANDARD FOR ENCODING VIDEO INFORMATION FOR PACKAGED MEDIA IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED WITHOUT A LICENSE UNDER APPLICABLE PATENTS IN THE MPEG-2 PATENT PORTFOLIO, WHICH LICENSE IS AVAILABLE FROM MPEG-LA,LLC AT THE ADDRESS ABOVE.
THIS PRODUCT IS LICENSED UNDER THE AVC PATENT PORTFOLIO LICENSE FOR THE PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL USE OF A CONSUMER TO (i) ENCODE VIDEO IN COMLIANCE WITH THE AVC STANDARD (“AVC VIDEO”) AND/OR (ii) DECODE AVC VIDEO THAT WAS ENCODED BY A CONSUMER ENGAGED IN A PERSONAL AND NON-COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY AND/OR WAS OBTAINED FROM A VIDEO PROVIDER LICENSED TO PROVIDE AVC VIDEO. NO LICENSE IS GRANTED OR SHALL BE IMPLIED FOR ANY OTHER USE. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM MPEG-LA.
You also acknowledge that no rights are granted or may be extended to you to use the SOFTWARE with MPEG-4 Video Content unless such MPEG-4 Content is sold or delivered to you by a content outlet licensed under the MPEG-4 Essential Claims to make such sale or delivery. 

* OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE
CyberLink retains the copyright, title and ownership of the SOFTWARE and the written materials ("Documentation") regardless of the form or media in or on which the original and other copies may exist.

* UPGRADES
If this copy of the SOFTWARE is an upgrade from an earlier version of the SOFTWARE, it is provided to you on a license exchange basis. Upon your installation and use of this copy of the SOFTWARE, you agree to voluntarily terminate your earlier EULA and you will not continue to use the earlier version of the SOFTWARE or resell or distribute it to another person or entity.

* USE OF MEDIA CONTENT LICENSED BY THIRD PARTIES
You may use pictures, audio, video, thumbnails or other media content (media content), if any, provided in the SOFTWARE, which may be licensed from third parties, to demonstrate or complete your work created by the use of the SOFTWARE; provided that you should not use the media content in any illegal, commercial or immoral manner, nor shall you grant your right to use to any third party. CyberLink does not provide any warranty or representation to these media content items from third parties and disclaims all liabilities to the maximum extent allowed by law.  

* LIMITED WARRANTY
CyberLink warrants the media on which the SOFTWARE is furnished to be free of defects in material and workmanship, under normal use, for a period of ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. If there is a defect in the media (CD/DVD-ROM), CyberLink's sole liability shall be to replace the defective media, which has been returned to CyberLink or the supplier with your dated invoice and is shown to be defective. In the event that CyberLink is unable to replace defective media, CyberLink shall at its sole discretion either refund your money upon your termination of this license or replace it with the newer version of the same software.

THIS SOFTWARE AND ACCOMPANYING DOCUMENTATION (INCLUDING INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE) ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND ARE NOT FAIL-SAFE. FURTHER, CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE, OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE, OF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IN TERMS OF CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CURRENTNESS, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE SOFTWARE IS ASSUMED BY YOU. IF THE SOFTWARE OR DOCUMENTATION IS DEFECTIVE, YOU, AND NOT CYBERLINK OR ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS, OR EMPLOYEES, ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICE, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

CYBERLINK DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER IT IS MADE BY CYBERLINK, ON THIS CYBERLINK PRODUCT. CYBERLINK DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY CYBERLINK, ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY OR IN ANY WAY INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THIS WARRANTY AND YOU MAY NOT RELY ON ANY SUCH INFORMATION OR ADVICE. 

NEITHER CYBERLINK NOR ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THIS PRODUCT SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE SUCH PRODUCT EVEN IF CYBERLINK HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Should any other warranties be found to exist, such warranties shall be limited in duration to ninety (90) days following the date of delivery to you. In no event will CyberLink's liability for any damages to you or any other person exceed the amount paid for the license to use the SOFTWARE.

You agree to bear the full, complete, and sole responsibility for using the SOFTWARE for any purpose. You also agree to indemnify and hold CyberLink harmless from any claims, proceedings, damages, costs, and expenses resulting from your use of the SOFTWARE for any illegal purpose or violation of this EULA.

Upon termination of this EULA, you should destroy the SOFTWARE and the Documentation and all the copies thereof and remove and delete the SOFTWARE from your hard disk or other storage device.

This EULA constitutes the entire agreement between you and CyberLink Corp. This EULA shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Taiwan and shall benefit CyberLink, its successors and assigns. 

Any claim or dispute between you and CyberLink or against any agent, employee, successor or assign of CyberLink, whether related to this EUL A or otherwise, and any claim or dispute related to this EULA or the relationship or duties contemplated under this EULA, including the validity of this arbitration clause, shall be resolved in Taipei, Taiwan, pursuant to the Taiwan Arbitration Act. 

This localized version of the EULA is for reference only. In case of inconsistencies between the localized version and the English version, the English version will prevail.